♪我已经觉得♪想再来一次，亲爱的
♪ I already feel ♪ Like doing it again, honey
因为一旦知道了，就知道了
♪ Cos once you know, then you know ♪
♬你不想回家♬你从哪里来♬就回哪里去
♪ And you don't wanna go home ♪ Back to wherever it is that you come from ♪
♪我只想和你在一起一直高
♪ I just wanna stay high ♪ With you
♪因为我的家乡♪每个人都跟♪皱眉走在一起
♪ Cos where I come from ♪ Everybody frowns and walks around with ♪
他们脸上那又老又丑的东西
♪ That old ugly thing on their face ♪
♬因为我来自哪里……——谢谢。
♪ Cos where I come from... - Thank you.
——再见。——再见。
- Ciao. - Bye.
♪我们努力工作♪我们整天磨磨蹭蹭的
♪ We work hard ♪ And we grind and we hustle all day ♪
♪总会有时间的，总会有时间的
♪ There comes a time, there comes a time ♪
晚上的时候，我们在哪里玩♬
♪ At night, where we come to play ♪
♬我们会微笑，笑♬跳♬鼓掌♬大喊大叫♬感觉，感觉很棒，是啊♬
♪ And we'll smiling, laughing ♪ Jumping, clapping ♪ Yelling and hollering ♪ Just feel, just feel great, yeah ♪
♪我只想和你一起高高在上♪
♪ I just want to stay high with you ♪
♪和你在一起♬一切都是一切♬一切都是美好的
♪ With you ♪ Everything is everything ♪ And everything is beautiful
♪你看，我所做的就是让它保持凉爽♪
♪ See, what I do is keep it cool ♪
♬不要担心大家现在在做什么
♪ And not worry 'bout what everyone is doing now ♪
♪我已经感觉♪想再来一次，亲爱的♪我只想保持兴奋…
♪ I already feel ♪ Like doing it again, honey ♪ I just wanna stay high...
♪我只想保持高…
♪ I just wanna stay high...
♪我只想和你一起嗨
♪ I just wanna stay high with you ♪
——你好!——我是狮子座。你一定是南希。
- Hello! - I'm Leo. You must be Nancy.
这是正确的。
That's right.
我可以进来吗?-是的，当然。是的,当然。
May I come inside? - Yes, of course. Yes, of course.
我可以吻你的脸颊吗?
May I kiss you on the cheek?
好的，可以。
Yes, that would be fine.
你闻起来很棒。——谢谢。
You smell wonderful. - Thank you.
它是什么?——可可·香奈儿。
What is it? - Coco Chanel.
奈杰尔·拉·劳森戴着它。
Nigel la Lawson wears it.
啊,奈杰尔。所以性感。
Ah, Nigel la. So sexy.
你不同意吗?
Don't you agree?
是的,不,我……我一直在等你说"以她的年龄"
Yes, no, I... I was waiting for you to say, "for her age".
大多数人说，当一个女人超过42岁，她是性感的“以她的年龄”。
Most people say, when a woman's over about 42, that she's sexy "for her age."
我在等待……我正等着呢。
I was waiting... I was waiting for that.
啊,对了。不，奈杰尔·拉·劳森在任何年龄都很性感。
Ah, right. Uh, no, Nigel la Lawson is empirically sexy, at any age.
嗨,南希?——是吗?
Hey, Nancy? - Yes?
我们会玩得很开心的。——好的。
We're gonna have a great time. - OK.
好的。
OK.
我告诉你我现在想要什么…什么?——喝。
I tell you what I'd love right now... What? - A drink.
喝一杯，当然，当然。对不起。
A drink, of course, of course. Sorry.
您要点什么?
What can I get you?
来杯汽酒舒缓一下我们的心情怎么样?
How about a glass of fizz to ease us into the mood.
一杯汽水。等一等。
A glass of fizz. Hold on.
请允许我。
Allow me.
给你。-非常感谢。
For you. - Thanks very much.
到经验上的性感。
To being empirically sexy.
是的。我要为此干杯。
Yes. I'll drink to that.
非常好的年份。
A very fine vintage.
从冰箱里拿的。
It's just from the minibar.
哦，你是说我。
Oh, you meant me.
我。-我只是在开玩笑。
Me. - I'm just teasing.
好,好。-我们坐下吧?
Righto, righto. - Shall we sit?
是的,我们坐。
Yes, let's sit.
那么，你会怎么…-那么，你喜欢音乐…的人吗?
So, what would you... - So, you enjoy music... by people?
是的,我做的。
Yeah, I do.
你喜欢什么样的音乐?
What kind of music do you like?
哦，我不知道。各种各样,嗯……抱歉，我有点分心，因为…因为近距离看你真的很好看。
Oh, I don't know. All sorts, um... Sorry, I'm a bit distracted cos, um... cos up close you really are very good-looking.
嗯-谢谢。
Mm. - Thank you.
比你照片上的还多。
Even more than in your photo.
啊，我更擅长3D。
Ah, I'm better in 3D.
我希望你收到…就合同。
I hope that you received, um... the contractual.
哦,钱?
Oh, the money?
钱，是的，抱歉。我不想太粗鲁，直接说出来。
The money, yes, sorry. I didn't want to be crass and just say it.
南希，相信我，靠工作赚钱并不是什么愚蠢的事。
There's nothing crass about getting paid for your work, Nancy, trust me on that.
谢谢，都收到了。
And thank you, it's all received.
你是爱尔兰人吗?-是的，我是。
Are you Irish? - Yes, I am.
你干这行很久了吗?
Have you been doing this long?
有一段时间了，是的。
A little while now, yeah.
长到足以知道一些事情。
Long enough to know some things.
你喜欢吗?
Do you enjoy it?
你知道吗?我喜欢，南希。
You know what? I love it, Nancy.
遇到各种各样的人，做各种各样的事……共同快乐。
Meeting all kinds of people, getting up to all sorts of things... mutual pleasure.
你不觉得……激怒了呢?
You don't feel... demeaned then?
不客气。
Not at all.
还是退化?——没有。
Or degraded? - No.
但是如果你遇到一个人，你真的只是…不想做?
But what if you meet someone and you really just... don't want to do it?
还没有发生。
Hasn't happened yet.
真的吗?——真的。
Really? - Really.
我觉得这很惊人。
I find that astonishing.
你有多少…-哦，绅士从不说。
How many have you... - Oh, a gentleman never tells.
哦，当然，是的。
Oh, of course, yes.
你不用担心，南希。今晚只有我们俩。
You don't have to worry, Nancy. This is just about us tonight.
那么，你的幻想是什么?
So, what is your fantasy?
嗯…我不确定你是否真的可以把它归类为幻想。
Um... I'm not sure you could really class it as a fantasy as such.
这有点平淡无奇。
It's a bit mundane for that.
好吧，你最想要的是什么?
OK, well, what would you most desire?
我的意思是，欲望从不平凡。
I mean, desires are never mundane.
嗯…
Um...
做爱……今晚，和你一起。
to have sex... tonight, um, with you.
就这些，真的。
That's about it, really.
的时刻。
For the moment.
太好了。-但你介意吗?
Great. - But do you mind?
你想要…我的意思是，我... ...可以说是失望吗?
Do you want... I mean, am I... ...a disappointment, so to speak?
好吗?
OK?
好吧,好吧。——充值吗?
OK, OK. - Top-up?
是的,请。
Yes, please.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
对不起，我只是受不了这种悬念。
I'm sorry, I just can't bear the suspense.
可以…我们可以……我们现在做可以吗?
Can... Could we... Would it be alright if we just did it now?
现在好些了吗?然后就结束了?
Right now? And get it over with?
结束这一切?——是的。
Get it over with? - Yes.
你注定要享受它。
You're meant to enjoy it.
不，我知道，我只是不擅长等待事情发生。
No, I know that, I'm just not very good at waiting for things to happen.
当它们发生的时候，我感觉好多了，我……恢复。
I'm much better when they've happened and I'm... recovering.
你说得好像这是场折磨。这不是强制性的。
You make it sound like it's an ordeal. It's not compulsory.
我们坐下来聊聊好吗?
Shall we just sit and chat for a bit?
哦，不，我不想那样做。
Oh no, I don't want to do that.
我不认为我们有很多共同点。
I don't think we'd have very much in common.
你可能会感到惊讶。-我很少感到惊讶。
You might be surprised. - I am very rarely surprised.
说实话，我喜欢合理地计划事情，尤其是为了避免意外。
I like to plan things properly, specifically in order to avoid being surprised, if I'm honest.
好吧，但我还是希望能给你个惊喜。
Fine, but I hope I can surprise you anyway.
N…不，我不想要那样的东西。
N... No, I don't want anything like that.
像什么?
Anything like what?
你知道，任何变态的东西。
You know, anything perverted.
哦，不，不，不。不是那种惊喜。
Oh, no, no, no. Not that kind of surprise.
太好了，我不喜欢任何东西进入专门为出来的东西设计的地方。
Oh good, I don't like anything going in to places that are designed for things to come out.
你说的是肛交?
You're talking about anal sex?
我不喜欢这个说法。
I don't like that phrase.
南希，我不会做任何你不希望我做的事。
Nancy, I won't be doing anything you don't want me to do.
我以前从没做过这样的事。
I've never done anything like this before.
我从来没有给自己买过这样的人……快乐。-…使用。
I've never bought anybody like this for my own... Pleasure. - ...use.
南希，听我说。我选择这样做。——是的。正确的。
Nancy, listen to me. I choose to do this. - Yes. Right.
你买的不是我，而是我的服务。
You know, you haven't bought me, you've bought my service.
我定了个价，你也同意了。
I set a price and you agreed.
我没有被剥削。
I'm not being exploited.
我不能忍受这种悬念。我受不了了。
I can't bear the suspense. I can't bear it.
期待吗?-是的…的失望。
The anticipation? - Yes... of disappointment.
为什么你认为你会失望?
Why do you assume you'll be disappointed?
因为我以前总是很失望。
Because I've always been disappointed before.
我需要…事实上，我想告诉你一件事。
I need to... Well, actually, I'd like to tell you something.
好的。
OK.
我从来没有高潮过。
I've never had an orgasm.
与合作伙伴吗?——与任何人。
With a partner? - With anyone.
还是自己?——没有。我自己也不行。
Or by yourself? - No. Not even by myself.
N…从来没有。
N... Never.
这是正确的。
That's right.
正确的。我明白了。
Right. I see.
这并不是一个挑战。-我还没把它当成。
It's not meant as a challenge. - I haven't taken it as one.
因为你无法实现它。- - - - - -很好。
Cos you won't be able to achieve it. - Fair enough.
你的自信很可爱，对这份工作无疑是必要的但我觉得我必须警告你，这是错的。
Your confidence is endearing, and no doubt necessary to the job but I feel I must warn you it is misplaced.
我不希望你为此感到难过因为我不会装的。我不会那样做的。不了。
Um, and I don't want you to feel bad about it because I won't be faking it. I don't do that. Not anymore.
我丈夫死后我做了一个决定再也不假装高潮了。
Um, I made a decision after my husband died never to fake an orgasm again.
他什么时候死的?
When did he die?
呃，两年前。它还为时过早。
Uh, two years ago. It was premature.
这是你第一次…此后遇到?是的。事实上，如果我们这样做，您将... ...只是我这辈子跟第二个男人发生过关系。
And is this your first... Encounter since then? Yes. In fact, if we do this, you will... ...only be the second man I have ever had sex with in my entire life.
好了，我说了。
There, I said it.
谢谢你告诉我。
Well, thank you for telling me.
如果你现在就走，我很乐意付我们约定金额的一半。
If you want to leave now, I'm very happy to pay half of what we agreed.
我不想离开，南希。
I don't want to leave, Nancy.
没什么能让我想离开。
Nothing is making me want to leave.
我不会离开除非我被明确指示或者我觉得我有人身危险。
I won't leave unless I'm clearly instructed to or I feel I'm in physical danger.
这种情况发生过吗?-是的。有几次。
Has that ever happened? - Yeah. A couple of times.
和一个女人吗?-是的。有一次和一个女人。
With a woman? - Yeah. Once with a woman.
嗯，她的丈夫，他想……他想玩3p。
Well, her husband, he thought... He wanted a threesome.
但事实证明他没有。
But it turned out he didn't.
她吗?——没有……但她确实想在一周后单独见面。
Did she? - No... but she did want to meet one-on-one a week later.
你做到了吗?——确定。
And did you do that? - Sure.
不是不诚实吗?——她的?
Wasn't that dishonest? - Of her?
的你。
Of you.
为什么?我是说，结婚的那个不是我。我只是在做我的工作。
Why? I mean, I'm not the married one. I'm just doing my job.
哇。
Wow.
这是一种教育。
It's all quite an education.
我希望它能继续下去。
I hope it continues.
你是漂亮的。
You're being saucy.
“漂亮的”?我奶奶以前常说"无礼"这个词。
"Saucy"? My grandmother used to say the word "saucy".
如果你不介意的话，我现在不想想你奶奶。
I'd rather not think about your grandmother right now if you don't mind.
没有问题。-我只是…无论如何……我只是想让你知道高潮的事。
No problem. - I just... Anyway... I just wanted to let you know about the orgasm thing.
我不指望会有，所以你可以放松点。
I'm not expecting one, so um, you can relax.
我放松。
I am relaxed.
这是个糟糕的主意。
This was a terrible idea.
你觉得自己在背叛你的丈夫吗?
Do you feel you're somehow betraying your husband?
我是说他的记忆。
His memory, I mean.
什么?哦，不，不，不，不。
What? Oh no, no, no, no, no.
不，不是那样的。——然后呢?
No, it's nothing like that. - Then what?
这不是我的风格，我是老师……我是个老师，我…我曾经给我的学生写过一篇关于性工作的道德问题的文章，现在我在这里……参与它。——南希。
It's just not very "me", I'm a teacher... Well, I was a teacher I... I used to set my pupils essays on the moral issues surrounding sex work and here I am... participating in it. - Nancy.
你可能是个很脆弱的年轻人，也许你是个孤儿。
You're probably a very vulnerable young man, maybe you're an orphan.
我不是孤儿。
I'm not an orphan.
是啊，也许你是在看护下长大的，你很自卑。
Yeah, or perhaps you grew up in care, you've got very low self-esteem.
我不是在寄养家庭长大的。
I didn't grow up in care.
你可能是被拐卖的，光看别人是看不出来的。-我不是被拐卖的。
You could've been trafficked against your will, you can't tell just by looking at somebody. - I wasn't trafficked against my will.
那我就不明白了。-你不明白什么?
Well, then I simply don't understand it. - You don't understand what?
你为什么要这么做。
Why you're doing this.
哦。好吧，如果你真的想知道我…我在用我做这些事赚的钱存大学学费。
Oh. Oh, well, if you really want to know I'm... I'm using the money I make doing this to save up for college.
哦。
Oh.
哦,多么美妙。你是真的吗?
Oh, how wonderful. Are you really?
不。
No.
哦。
Oh.
南希，你不用再担心我了…-…让我们把这个移到你身上。
Nancy, you need to stop worrying about me... - ...let's move this back to you.
好的。哦,上帝。——现在,南希……这太疯狂了，太可怕了，这是不对的。——南希。
OK. Oh, God. - Now, Nancy... This is crazy, it's terrible, it's wrong. - Nancy.
我的儿子……我的儿子会震惊的。
My son... My son would be appalled.
南希。——是的。
Nancy. - Yes.
我们去睡觉吧。——好的。
Let's go to bed. - OK.
好吗?
OK?
好的。——好。
OK. - Good.
过来。——嗯。
Come here. - Mm-hmm.
这样可以吗?
Is this OK?
好吗?
OK? - Mm.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
听着，如果你，需要带走任何我不介意的东西。
Listen, er, if you, um, need to take anything that's fine by me.
我很好,南希。
I'm fine, Nancy.
我指的是法律方面的东西，你知道，帮助……都在下面了。-不，我向你保证，都很有效。
I mean legal things, you know, to help... with it all down there. - No, I assure you, it all works.
我知道，我只是…不，我明白你的意思，但我不需要什么蓝色小药丸。
I know, I mean, I just... No, I know what you mean, but I don't need any little blue pills.
从来没有吗?——从来没有。
Never? - Never.
但是如果你不喜欢这个人呢?
But what if you don't fancy the person?
我是说，你不能强迫自己，如果你不这么做的话。
I mean, you can't force yourself, surely, if you don't.
总有一些东西值得想象。
There's always something to fancy.
不,没有。——有。
No, there isn't. - There is.
哦。
Oh.
你做过的最老的人是谁?
What's the oldest person you've ever done it with?
南希，你说得太简单了。
That's a bit reductive, Nancy.
“还原”，这是个好词。我喜欢它。
"Reductive", that's a good word. I like it.
是的，这是个好词。
Yes, it is a good word.
我很高兴你喜欢它。我只是为你选的。
I'm glad you like it. I chose it just for you.
但说真的，我真的很想知道，多大了?
But seriously actually I really do want to know, how old?
八十二年。-八十二吗?
Eighty-two. - Eighty-two?
是的。-八十二!
Yes. - Eighty-two!
是的。-八十二。
Yeah. - Eighty-two.
南希。
Nancy.
好的，我现在感觉好多了。——好的。
OK, I'm feeling a bit better now. - OK.
嗯…那么，我身上有什么能让你尽你所能抓住的?
Um... So, what's the little thing about me that you can hold onto with all your might?
让你活在当下?
To make you come alive in the moment?
到这里来。
Come here.
我喜欢你的嘴。
I like your mouth.
我喜欢你脖子的线条，一直到这里。
I like the line of your neck, down to about here.
这……它是如此优雅。
And this... it's so elegant.
嗯,只是……等一下。
Um, just... hang on a second.
我就,嗯……我去趟洗手间换身衣服。
I'll just, um... I'll just go to the bathroom and change.
好的，但是不要改变太多。
OK, but don't change too much.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
哒哒。
Ta-dah.
噢!
Ooh!
你看起来很好。
You look great.
哦，嗯，一切都好吗?
Oh, um, everything OK?
是的，只是，我不喜欢玛氏巧克力棒。我能闻到。
Yes, it's just, I don't like Mars bars. I can smell it.
这有点令人不快。
It's a bit off-putting.
哦,对不起,对不起。我去洗洗牙。
Oh, sorry, sorry. I'll go and clean my teeth.
你介意吗?谢谢你！
Would you mind? Thank you.
这是什么?
What's this?
很好。-我又改变主意了。
Very nice. - I've changed my mind again.
我不想做。很抱歉浪费了你的时间。
I don't want to do it. I'm sorry to have wasted your time.
你……我仍然会支付。
You... I'll still pay.
但你可以穿好衣服走了。
But you can get dressed and go.
这不是为了玛氏巧克力吧?
This isn't about the Mars bar, is it?
不，不是玛氏巧克力的事。
No, it's not about the Mars bar.
你不觉得我有吸引力吗?
Do you not find me attractive?
别荒谬。
Don't be ridiculous.
你清楚…美学完美，显然也足够好。
You're clearly... aesthetically perfect, and apparently nice enough.
你想象中会发生什么，我是说…如果你不想做，为什么要预约我?
What did you picture happening, I mean... why did you book me if you don't want to do it?
我现在还不知道。一时的疯狂，仅此而已。
I don't know at this point. A moment of madness, that's all.
这是所有。
That's all.
你经常有这样的疯狂时刻吗?
Do you regularly have moments of madness like this?
不。
No.
你通常会做出理性的决定吗?
Do you usually make rational decisions?
是的。
Yes.
那这次又有什么不同?
Then why would this be any different?
你肯定是有原因的。
I mean, you must have had a reason.
让你这么做的东西。我打赌你几天前就想过了。
Something that made you do it. I bet you thought about it for days before.
周……个月。年,也许。
Weeks... Well, months. Years, perhaps.
那就不是疯狂的时刻了。
Well, then it's not a moment of madness.
这就是你想要的，南希。
This is what you want, Nancy.
现在你有了，为什么不接受呢?
And now that you have it, why won't you take it?
你想要的东西明明就在这里，触手可及，你为什么不拿呢。
Why won't you take what you want when it's right here, within reach.
哦，我不知道。突然之间就有了争议。
Oh, I don't know. It feels controversial suddenly.
我不觉得它有争议。
I don't find it controversial.
想要这样的东西。甚至想要它。
To want something like this. Even to want it.
如果你想要的只是性不是有一堆男人愿意和你上床吗?
If it's just sex you want aren't there a dozen men around who'd love to hook up with you?
如果一切都太过……我是说，他们当然想这么做。
If it's all too much... I mean, surely they want to.
哦,是的…是的，他们有，嗯……是的，罗伯特死后他们就说得很清楚了但是，是我，我不想。
Oh, yeah... Yes, they do, um... Yes, they made that very clear actually since Robert died but um, it's me, I don't want to.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
他们都老了。
They're all old.
老男人。我不想要一个老头。我想要一个年轻的。
Old men. I don't want an old man. I want a young one.
一个年轻的身体。没有销赃，我必须付钱，我当然要付钱。
A young body. And no of fence, I have to pay for that, of course I do.
我来了，我没有被冒犯。
Well, I'm here, and I'm not offended.
你怎么还在这?
Actually, why are you still here?
我只是想付你一晚上的钱，让你做你想做的事。
I've just offered to pay you to spend an evening doing whatever you please.
你怎么还在这里?
Why are you still here?
我很感兴趣。——什么?
I'm interested. - In what?
在你。-哦，看在上帝的份上，不必对我屈尊俯就。——我不是。
In you. - Oh, for Heaven's sakes no need to patronise me. - I'm not.
你是矛盾的。
You're conflicted.
矛盾是有趣的。
Conflicted is interesting.
你以前没见过拿不定主意的女人吗?我不相信。
You've never met a woman who can't make up her mind before? I don't believe that.
我曾遇到过这样的女人，她们无法决定午餐吃哪个三明治，但如果我们最终在一间卧室里，她们通常知道自己想要什么。
I've met women who can't decide which sandwich to have for lunch but if we've ended up in a bedroom together, they usually know what they want at that point.
嗯，年轻女性不一样。
Well, young women are different.
是的，我想是的。
Yes, I think they are.
和我们以前不一样了…嗯，就是我年轻时的样子。
Different to how we were... well, how I was when I was young.
反正我也不是什么社会叛逆者。
I wasn't actually a social renegade, anyway.
我有几个朋友是，但我们放学后就失去联系了。
A couple of my friends were, but we lost touch after school.
但那时的伦敦是另一个国家。
But London was a different country back then.
我们其他人还停留在20世纪50年代，这是压制性的。
The rest of us were stuck in the 1950s, it was repressive.
对不起。
Sorry.
我也不像她们现在穿着劈腿裙，跳萨尔萨舞之类的，对性充满自信。
And I wasn't brimming with sexual confidence like they all are now with their thigh-split dresses and salsa classes and whatnot.
我是说，人们把跳钢管舞作为一种爱好。
I mean, people do pole dancing for a hobby.
我读过，我读过一篇关于它的文章。
I've read about it, I read an article about it.
我是说，爱好?
I mean, a hobby?
Wh……我…天啊，我听起来好老。
Wh... I... Christ, I sound so old.
我知道我听起来很老，但是里奥，你见过以跳钢管舞为爱好的人吗?
I know I sound old, but Leo, did you ever meet anyone who does pole dancing for a hobby?
我想那主要是为时髦女孩准备的。
I think that's mainly for posh girls.
是的，你可能是对的。
Yes, you're probably right.
我是说，我认识钢管舞演员，但他们不会付钱的。
I mean, I know pole dancers but they wouldn't pay to do it.
那只是一些该死的经济学，你明白我的意思吗?
That's just some fucked up economics, do you know what I mean?
不完全是，但我是说，我能想象。
Not really, but I mean, I can imagine.
我对这个世界不太了解。
It's not a world I know much about.
一个订了酒店和一名性工作者过夜的女人说的。
Says the woman who booked a hotel and a sex worker for the night.
哦,上帝。哦，哦，你说得对。
Oh, God. Oh, oh, you're right.
天啊，我就是个下流的老变态。
Oh, God, I'm just a seedy old pervert.
那就去吧。很恶心。我突然觉得自己像罗尔夫·哈里斯了。
Just go. It's disgusting. I feel like Rolf Harris all of a sudden.
罗尔夫·哈里斯?
Rolf Harris?
不要紧。
Never mind.
来吧，我们上床吧。
Come on, let's get in the bed.
-我们去盖被子吧
- Let's get under the covers.
为什么他们要把这些东西做成……穿紧身衣?
Why do they make these things like... getting into a straight-jacket?
这是荒谬的。
It's ridiculous.
你真正想要的生活是什么?
What do you really want to do with your life?
我想在死之前看到维纳斯。
I'd like to see, er, Venus before I die.
好的。
OK.
我只是好奇你是什么感觉。
I'm just curious about what it's like for you.
你显然很聪明。
You're clearly very bright.
你为什么这么说?
What makes you say that?
我是一名教师，我知道有些人会用“经验主义”这个词
Well, I'm a teacher, and I know there are some people who use the word "empirically"
在谈话中，有很多人不这样做。
in a conversation, and there are very many who don't.
聪明的人会这么做。
And the clever ones are those that do.
我用了吗?
Did I use it?
是的。奈杰尔。“经验性感”。和“还原”。
Yes. Nigel la. "Empirically sexy". And "reductive".
哦，是的，你说得对。所以我所做的。
Oh, yes, you're right. So I did.
怎么，你不觉得这是聪明人的工作，是吗?
So, what, you don't think this is a job for clever people, is that it?
不!不不，我不是那个意思。不。
No! No, no, I didn't mean that. No.
不，我只是问资历…你上学了吗?
No, I was just asking about qualifications and... Did you go to school?
当然可以。我的意思是，我母亲是一个非常严格的爱尔兰天主教徒。
Of course. I mean, my mother was a very strict Irish Catholic.
她对你现在做的事怎么看?
And what does she think about what you're doing now?
你想谈谈我妈妈吗?真的吗?
You want to talk about my mother? Really?
是你提起她的。-现在我放弃了。
Well, you brought her up. - Well now I'm dropping it.
但认真…
But seriously...
她不知道。
She doesn't know.
你穿这个看起来好性感。
You know, this looks so sexy on you.
她认为你是做什么的?
What does she think you do?
如果我告诉你，我们能放弃吗?
If I tell you, can we drop it?
因为你穿这个真的很好看。
Because you really do look good in this.
我保证。
I promise.
她以为我在钻井平台工作。
She thinks I work on an oil rig.
一个石油钻井平台?
An oil rig?
是的，一个钻井平台。在北海。
Yes, an oil rig. In the North Sea.
没有,但是……但做……你们保持联系吗?你会把钻井平台上的最新情况发给她吗?-南希，你答应过的。
No, but... But do... Do you keep in contact? Do you send her updates about life on the oil rig? - Now, Nancy, you promised.
但你怎么知道在石油钻塔上会发生什么?
But how do you know what happens on an oil rig?
你知道，我知道。
I Google it, you know.
我发现了一个网站，上面有关于石油钻井平台生活的故事，我有时会复制粘贴它们。
I found a website where there's stories about life on an oil rig and I copy and paste them sometimes.
哈哈。这是惊人的。什么生活。
Ha. That's amazing. What a life.
哦,亲爱的。与此同时，我儿子在大学攻读硕士学位。
Oh, dear. Meanwhile, my son's doing his Masters at university.
你不高兴吗?
Are you not happy about that?
是啊，不，我很高兴，我当然很高兴。
Oh, yes, no, I am, of course I'm happy.
太棒了。
It's great.
我为什么会不高兴呢?这正是我们所期望的。
Why wouldn't I be happy? It's just what's expected.
你为什么听起来这么矛盾?
Why do you sound so ambivalent about it?
"矛盾"，这是另一个好词。——嗯。
"Ambivalent", that's another good word. - Mm-hmm.
所以…你的儿子吗?
So... your son?
是的,好吧,我……我…我…哦亲爱的。
Yes, well, I... I... I... Oh dear.
我从没对别人说过这话，太可怕了。
I've never said this to anyone before, this is awful.
没关系，我该告诉谁呢?
It's OK, who am I going to tell?
来吧。
Come on.
我…事实上我觉得他很无趣。
I... well, the truth is I find him boring.
你觉得你自己的儿子很无聊?
You find your own son boring?
是的。太可怕了，不是吗?
Yes. That's awful, isn't it?
我从没听人这么说过。
I've just never heard anyone say that before.
你总是觉得他很无趣吗?
Have you always found him boring?
不,不总是正确的。不，他是个很好的男孩。
No, not always. No, he's a very nice boy.
他很容易被人猜到，就像他父亲一样。
He's just very predictable, like his father.
他学习什么?
What's he studying?
化学。请忘记我说过的话。
Chemistry. Please forget I said that.
算了吧，他是个可爱的男孩，我非常爱他，我应该感激他，因为他变得很好。
Just forget it, he's a lovely boy and I love him very much and I should be grateful because he's turned out very well.
还有其他孩子吗?
Any other kids?
女儿。老了。我们合不来。
Mm. Daughter. Older. We don't get along.
哦,为什么不呢?
Oh, why not?
她觉得我很冷。
She thinks I'm cold.
你觉得怎么样?
And what do you think?
我不觉得我冷。
I don't think I'm cold.
我的意思是，我的内心并不冷，但也许我对她很冷是因为她一直都很夸张。
I mean, I don't feel cold inside but maybe I'm cold with her because she's so over the top all the time.
和她哥哥相反。
So the opposite to her brother.
她住在巴塞罗那，生活在这种放荡不羁的环境中。
She lives in Barcelona, in this bohemian set-up.
他们都是艺术家，虽然我从没见过真正的艺术作品。
They're all artists, although I've never seen any actual art.
除非你的艺术是烧你父母的钱，那…事实上，这不是不可能的。
Unless the art consists of burning your parents' money, which... Actually, it's not out of the question.
至少她不无聊。
At least she's not boring.
不，不，是这样的。有这一点。
No, no, there is that. There is that.
你的孩子让你失望了，南希。
So your children have disappointed you, Nancy.
是的。但你最后一次见到你妈妈是什么时候?
Yes. But when did you last see your mum?
为什么?
Why?
因为我对你来自哪里很感兴趣。
Cos I'm interested in where you come from.
我不是来自任何地方。
I don't come from anywhere.
其实我是在一小片豆子大小的蘑菇下被发现的，是友好的狼养大的。
You know, I was actually found under a little patch of mushrooms size of a bean, raised by friendly wolves.
哦,继续。告诉我一些。
Oh, go on. Tell me something.
我敬畏任何成为母亲的人。
I'm in awe of anyone who becomes a mother.
世界上最辛苦的工作。
Hardest job in the world.
你是从妈妈网还是什么网站上查到的?
Did you get that off Mumsnet or something?
抱歉?
Sorry?
这有点笼统。不是所有的母亲都是好的。
It's a bit general. Not all mothers are good.
-我不知道-我只吃过一个。
- Well, I wouldn't know. - I've only had one.
是啊，我们都被我们得到的东西困住了，不是吗?
Yeah, we're all stuck with whatever we get, aren't we?
父母和孩子都一样。
Parents and children alike.
但至少我知道我的孩子在干什么。
At least I know what mine are up to, though.
你就没想过你儿子是否对你隐瞒了他的生活吗?
Haven't you ever wondered if your son is lying to you about his life?
不。——为什么不呢?
No. - Why not?
也许他不想让你失望。
Maybe he doesn't want to disappoint you.
他有搭档吗?
Has he got a partner?
是的。好女孩，也很无聊。
Yes. Nice girl, also boring.
接受小学教师培训。无聊,无聊,无聊。
Training to be a primary school teacher. Boring, boring, boring.
你不是说你是个老师吗?
I thought you said you were a schoolteacher?
是啊，但我是中学的宗教教育老师。这是一个非常不同的野兽…和六岁的孩子一起涂色。
Yeah, but I was a Religious Education teacher in a secondary school. That's a very different beast to... colouring in with six-year-olds.
他们说初等教育是最重要的。
They say primary education is the most important.
嗯,他们错了。
Well, they're wrong.
你知道有多少中学生认为宗教教育值得他们花一盎司的时间和精力吗?
Do you know what proportion of secondary school students think that Religious Education is worth even an ounce of their time and attention?
我的意思是,我…-不，没错。
I mean, I... - No, well, exactly.
完全正确。所以我就这样，年复一年地讲着同样的老东西，无法脱离课程，以防我从头脑那里得到抱怨，而无法问他们
Exactly. So there I would be, year after year spouting the same old stuff, unable to break away from the curriculum in case I got complaints from the head and unable to ask them
任何真实的东西，以防我们浪费时间，努力完成工作，让他们通过考试，然后第二年你又要重新开始
anything real in case we lost time and just battling through the work and getting them through the exams and then you just start again the following year
还是老样子。这太无聊了。
doing the same old stuff. It was just stultifying.
我可能破坏了气氛。
I think I may have killed the mood.
我不确定当时有什么气氛。
I'm not sure there was a mood.
对不起，我太失礼了。-不，这是真的
I'm sorry, that was rude of me. - No, it's true.
不，但你不是在为真相买单。
No, but you're not paying for the truth, though.
你是在为幻想买单。
You're paying for a fantasy.
现在，我不确定我在为什么付钱。
At this moment, I'm not sure what I'm paying for.
我可以给你看。
I can show you.
我不怀疑。
I don't doubt it.
什么能让你恢复心情?
What would get you back in the mood?
嗯?
Hmm?
你丈夫会怎么做才能让一切重新开始?
What would your husband do to get it all going again?
嗯…嗯…他……他,呃……脱掉他所有的衣服，躺在床上，不穿睡衣。
Um... Well... He... He would, er... take all his clothes off, and lie in the bed without putting his pyjamas on.
我会脱掉所有的衣服穿上睡衣躺在他旁边他会抚摸我的肩膀和胸部然后他会爬到上面，做这些事
And I would take all my clothes off put my nightie on and lie in the bed next to him and then he would rub my shoulders and breasts a bit and then he would climb on top, do the business
吻我的脸颊，滚下来，穿上他的睡衣，继续睡觉。
kiss my cheek, roll off, put his pyjamas on and go back to sleep.
就这些吗?——就是这样。
That's it? - That's it.
总是?——永远。
Always? - Always.
31年无偏差。
No deviation for 31 years.
这就是你唯一一次做爱吗?
And that's the only sex you've ever had?
正确的。
Correct.
哇。
Wow.
“哇”。
"Wow" indeed.
没有口语?
No oral?
没有口服。-连他身上都没有?
No oral. - Not even on him?
不，他说那很有辱人格。
No, he said it was demeaning.
为你?——为他。
For you? - For him.
好吧……好吧，我猜他对你也一样吧?
OK... OK, and I presume it was the same for him on you?
是的，他说那对他来说也是一种侮辱。
Yes, he said that was demeaning for him too.
所以，你从来没有……不，我从来没有。
So, you've never had... No, I've never had.
从来没有。
Never given.
你想要吗?
Do you want to?
是的,我喜欢。我想。
Yes, I do. I want to.
我非常想。
I want to very much.
我一直都是这样。
I always have done.
对不起。
Sorry.
我很抱歉要哭了。
I'm sorry to cry.
它是愚蠢的。
It's stupid.
我,嗯…我认为……
I, um... I think that...
当我还是个…十几岁的时候，我父母带我去希腊度假嗯，这是一生一次的旅行，无论如何，对他们来说，而且……嗯…
Well, when I was a... a teenager my parents took me to Greece on holiday um, it was a once-in-a-lifetime trip, for them, anyway, and... um...
酒店里有个服务员，我想他大概20岁左右，他看着我，就像我……这是他见过的最美味的东西，我感觉我的身体在水里。
at the hotel there was this waiter, I think he was about 20 and he looked at me like I was... the most delicious thing he'd ever seen and I felt my body go to water.
有一天晚上，他下班后在附近晃悠，我很热，所以我在我父母睡觉后去了花园，他在那里，抽着烟，嗯……我站在
And one night, he was hanging around after his shift and um, I was hot so I went out into the garden after my parents had gone to bed and he was there, smoking a cigarette and, um... I stood
在这棵长满粉红色小花、面朝大海的小灌木前……
in front of this little bush covered in tiny pink flowers looking out to sea...
他一言不发地走了上来，... ...吻了我的脖子，把他的手伸进我的裙子和内裤里，我能感觉到他在下面滑来滑去，我把自己推回到他身上
and without a word, he came up and... ... kissed my neck and put his hand under my skirt and into my knickers and I could feel him sliding around down there and I was pushing myself back into him
这是我经历过的最疯狂、最兴奋的感觉……然后一辆车启动了车头灯亮了他被吓了一跳，就跑了。
and it was the most crazy, exciting feeling I'd ever had and... and, um, then a car started up and the headlamps came on and he was startled so he dashed away.
第二天我们就回家了。
And the next day we went home.
我真希望我们能多待一天。
And I wished we'd just stayed one more day.
你好。——你好了。
Hello. - Hello again.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这真是个惊喜。
This is a very nice surprise.
是吗?
Is it?
还是那个房间。我订了同样的房间因为我不想被新的布局搞砸。
It's the same room. I mean, I booked the same room cos I didn't want to be thrown by a new layout.
不，我是说你又登记我了。
Oh, no, I mean you booking me again.
哦。-我是说，你上次一定很满意，所以我很高兴。
Oh. - I mean, you must've been satisfied the last time, so I'm happy about that.
是的，是的，我很满意。是的。
Yes, yes, I was satisfied. Yes.
但是呢?
But?
听起来好像会有个"但是"
Oh, it sounded like there was going to be a "but".
不，不，不是特别喜欢。
No, no, not particularly.
我，嗯，我得到了一些反馈和一些这次的目标。
I, um, I've got a little bit of feedback and a couple of attainment goals for this time.
是的,我明白了。确定。好的。
Right, I see. Sure. OK.
你想喝点什么吗?-是的。
Would you like a drink? - Yeah.
这听起来太棒了。
That sounds great.
——干杯。
- Cheers.
所以，我把我想做的事情列了一个清单。
So, I've made a list of things that I'd like to get through.
听起来很性感。
Oh, that sounds sexy.
不要嘲笑我。我是一个老师。
Don't mock me. I'm a teacher.
旧习难改。
Old habits die hard.
清单上的第一个是什么?
What's first on the list?
一号:
Number one:
我给你口交。
I perform oral sex on you.
你给我口交。
you perform oral sex on me.
我们做一个"69"
we do a "69"
如果现在还这么叫的话。
if that's what it's still called.
呃，我不知道。
Uh, I don't know.
我在上面。小狗式的。
me on top. doggy-style.
嗯，这听起来都很可行。
Well, that all sounds very achievable.
哦,是吗?哦,很好。
Oh, does it? Oh, good.
好的,因为我…我没有参照系。
Good, cos I'm... I have no frame of reference.
我试过，在网上查过，但坦白说，这很令人担忧。
I've tried, um, looking on the internet, but it's alarming, frankly.
我是说，如果你输入"经典色情片"就会弹出12个勃起窗口。
I mean, if you type in "classy porn" to Google up pop 12 windows of erections.
我是说，根本就没有任何铺垫。我预定的时间够吗?
I mean, there's no build-up at all. Have I booked enough time?
你想今天就做完吗?
You want to do it all today?
是的,如果可能的话。
Yes, if possible.
我是说，你的费用太贵了我不确定在这之后我是否还能负担得起另一次治疗。
I mean, it's just, you're quite expensive and I'm not sure if I'll be able to afford another session after this.
好的。
OK.
我明白了,嗯……难道就没有其他应该在名单上的东西吗?
I understand, um... Isn't there something else that should be on that list?
像什么?
Like what?
好吧，我希望你能完全满意……如果可能的话。
Well, I'd love for you to feel completely satisfied... if at all possible.
哦。
Oh.
-实际上是大o。
- The big "o", in fact.
是的。
Yes.
不，我喜欢一份完全可以打勾的清单。
No, I like a list that can be fully ticked-off.
可以实现的目标。那是通往幸福的道路，祈求月亮没有意义。
Achievable goals. That's the path to happiness, there's no point in wishing for the moon.
嗯，这是高潮，你知道的，这不是Fabergé卵子。
Well, it's an orgasm, you know, it's not a Fabergé egg.
人们每天都有。
People have them every day.
正确的。你知道吗，你是对的。这都说得通。
Right. Do you know what, you're right. That all makes sense.
我只是…我想要有成就感。
I just... I want to feel a sense of achievement.
是的。-我不想走开…从这种未解决的感觉。
Yes. - I don't want to walk away... from this feeling unresolved.
我可以吗?
May I?
你知道吗?
Do you know what?
我们今天会尽可能多地这样做。
We'll do as much of this as we can today.
我认为我们肯定会取得重大进展。
I think we'll certainly make a significant dent in it.
好。
Good.
这很好。好。
That's good. Good.
你想从口交开始吗?
You want to start with the blow job?
是的，我想是的。
Yes, I think so.
先把大的拿出来。
Get the big one out the way first.
我应该跪吗?
Should I kneel?
我可以站在椅子上，但通常不是这么做的。
Well, I could stand on a chair, but that's not how it's usually done.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
你不用做这些的。
You don't have to do any of this.
我知道，我…但我想成为一个通情达理的女人。
No, I know, I... but I want to be a woman of the world.
我是说，还有比我更有性经验的修女呢。
I mean, there are nuns out there with more sexual experience than me.
这是令人尴尬的。你想让我刷牙吗?
It's embarrassing. Do you want me to brush my teeth?
什么?不。南希，你可以…你可以放手。
What? No. Nancy, you can just... you can just let go.
放手吗?我到底要放弃什么?
Let go? What am I letting go of, exactly?
我是说，我们需要一些计划，不是吗?
I mean, we need some sort of plan, don't we?
我不想在枝形吊灯上荡来荡去，弄出动物的叫声。
I don't want to swing from the chandeliers and make loud animal noises.
我想看看。
I'd like to see that.
你在释放内心的东西。
You're letting go of the thing inside that grips you.
你知道，那是对你的评判。
You know, that judges you.
从外面看着你的人。
That watches you from the outside.
天啊，如果我放手，什么事都有可能发生。
Christ, if I let go of that, anything might happen.
那是唯一能让我活下去的东西。
That's the only thing keeping my life together.
让它一直走下去……在这里吗?
Keeping it ticking along... Here?
在这里。
Over here.
我该怎么做?
What am I just supposed to do?
就像自由漂浮的水母一样，等着什么东西浮上来?
Just float around like some sort of free form jellyfish you know, waiting for something to come up?
不,但是你……-我解开你的腰带吗?
No, but you're... - Do I undo your belt?
你能撤销吗?正常是什么?
Do you undo it? What's normal?
嗯，更重要的是…-好吧，我来。
Well, it's more a matter of... - Well, I'll do it.
好的。
OK.
不,我只是……我只想给你吹箫。
No, I just... I just want to do a blow job.
我想把它排好然后我们可以在规定的时间内尽可能多地处理这个列表的其他部分。-我们有两节课
I want to get that sorted and then we can work through as much of the rest of the list as we can in the allotted time. - Like we've got a double lesson
口头讨论的时间表，然后我们可以看看下午还剩下什么?
timetabled for oral, and then we can see what's left of the afternoon?
完全正确。-会议结束时我要按铃吗?
Exactly. - And shall I ring a bell at the end of the session?
你用铃吗?上次你没有。
Do you use a bell? You didn't last time.
哦。
Oh.
很有趣。
Very funny.
嗯…哦……对不起。
Um... Oh... Sorry.
我待会再讲这些。
I'll be back to all this in just a second.
嗨,亲爱的。嗨。
Hi, darling. Hi.
很抱歉。——一切都好吗?
Sorry about that. - Everything OK?
是的。我的女儿。她只是现在有点小麻烦，可以这么说吧。
Yes. My daughter. She's just in a bit of a pickle at the moment, shall we say.
听到这个消息我很难过。
I'm sorry to hear that.
这不是第一次，也不会是最后一次。
Well, it's not the first time, won't be the last.
她以前经常给她父亲打电话说这些，但不管怎样…我们能不能试着做点力所能及的事?
She used to ring her father about all this, but anyway... Um, shall we just try and get through what we can?
考试前?-嗯,是的。
Before the exam? - Um, yes.
南希。
Nancy.
没有考试。一切都是舞蹈。
There is no exam. It's all a dance.
我不知道舞步。
I don't know the steps.
即兴舞蹈，我们随它去。
An improvised dance, we just go where it takes us.
没有时间表，没有铃响。
There's no timetable, there's no bell.
但我只付了两个小时的钱。
But I've only paid for two hours.
那我们就好好享受吧。每一分钟。
Well, then let's enjoy them. Every single minute.
好吧，来吧。
OK, come on then.
你想从口交开始还是从单子上的其他事开始?
Do you want to start with the blow job or go with something else on the list?
不，我想我要按顺序去。
No, I think I'd like to go in order.
我觉得我已经准备好吹箫了。
I feel like I'm prepared for the blow job now.
罗伯特，我的丈夫，他从来没有……他从来不想尝试新事物。
Robert, my husband, he never... he never wanted to try anything new.
他策划了一切，甚至他自己的葬礼。
He planned everything, I mean, even his own funeral, actually.
我很害怕他会在那天出现，告诉我三明治里放错了火腿。
I was terrified he'd turn up on the day and tell me I'd put the wrong ham in the sandwiches.
这不是一个……激情的熔炉烧坏了我们的关系，这更像是，嗯……AGA最下面的抽屉
It wasn't a... furnace of passion that burnt out our relationship, it was more like, um... the bottom drawer of an AGA.
一个什么?
A what?
这是个老式的炉子。
Um, it's an old-fashioned stove.
你关不掉它。
You can't turn it off.
它不停地发出咔嗒声，在底部有一个类似冷却器的抽屉，你可以把东西推到……你知道的，慢慢煮
It keeps on chugging away, and at the bottom there's a kind of cooler drawer thing that you can push things to the back of... Mm. - ...you know, to cook them slowly
比如一碗炖苹果什么的。
like a bowl of stewed apples or something.
我明白了。——对吗?
I see. - Do you?
呃,不是真的。
Er, not really.
但是，我想你的意思是你的婚姻发展缓慢是因为你把它推到了后面。
But, um, I think you mean your marriage stewed slowly because you pushed it to the back.
然后就忘了。
And then forgot about it.
好吧,不管怎样。他走了，一切都没了。
Well, anyway. He's gone, it's all gone.
古老的历史。
Ancient history.
我想尝试一些新的东西。
And I want to try something new.
然后,很好。
Then, good.
所以，我需要把口交做好。
So, I need to get that blow job under my belt.
很明显,你的腰带。
Your belt, obviously.
好的。
OK.
好吗?
OK?
好,好,看。
OK, OK, look.
我有个主意。
I have an idea.
你喜欢跳舞，对吧?
You like dancing, right?
只有在没人看的时候。
Only when nobody's watching.
好吧，那我们来改变一下气氛。
OK, well then we're gonna change the mood.
我要放点音乐你要像没人看一样跳舞。
I'm gonna put on some music and you're gonna dance like nobody is watching.
来吧，南希·斯托克斯。
Come on, Nancy Stokes.
来和我跳支舞吧。
Come have a dance with me.
♬你上楼来，但不是来说话的
♪ Well, you come upstairs but not to talk ♪
♬你待了一会儿，然后走了一小段路回家
♪ You stay a little while then you do a little walk on home ♪
♬我听见你在楼下抽烟
♪ I hear you downstairs smoking cigarettes ♪
♬我听到你在说什么♬因为你没什么可说的
♪ I hear you talking shit ♪ Cos you ain't got nothing to talk about at all ♪
所以你带我去派对，让我注意到♬
♪ So you took me to the party and got me to notice ♪
♬你想要感觉好点，但你觉得自己要爆炸了
♪ That you wanna feel good and you feel like you're gonna explode ♪
♪好吧，我不在乎，不能关注♪
♪ Well, I don't care, can't pay attention ♪
♬我一点也不在乎你的意图
♪ And I don't give a damn about your intentions at all ♪
♪哦一点点
♪ Ooh wee
♬把威士忌递给我，把杜松子酒递给我
♪ Well, pass me the whisky, pass me the gin ♪
♬把车里剩下的饮料递给我
♪ Pass me whatever there's drink left in ♪
♬我才不管现在是不是早上7点呢
♪ Well, I don't care if it's seven in the morning ♪
♪我只在乎这可能是第二次♪
♪ For all I care it could be the second coming ♪
♬你说你再也受不了了
♪ Well, you say you can't take it anymore ♪
♬你不能这样生活，这真的是很重要的
♪ You can't live like this, it's a really big deal ♪
♪好吧，我不在乎，不能关注♪
♪ Well, I don't care, can't pay attention ♪
♬我一点也不在乎你的意图
♪ And I don't give a fuck about your intentions at all ♪
♪哦,哦
♪ Ooh, ooh
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
哦,上帝,上帝。
Oh, God, God.
那又会是我女儿了。
That'll be my daughter again.
她总是按两次铃。
She always rings twice.
她总是忘记最重要的信息，不得不回电话。
She always forgets the most crucial bit of information and has to ring back.
好的。-我不想接。
OK. - I don't want to answer it.
那就不要。-但我总是接的。
Then don't. - But I always answer it.
即使你不想?
Even when you don't want to?
是啊，尤其是我不想的时候。——好的。
Yeah, especially when I don't want to. - OK.
那我该说什么?
Well, what am I gonna say?
"你好，亲爱的，很抱歉我现在不能说话因为我已经和这个男人约好了今晚我想鼓起勇气给他口交"
"Hello darling, I'm sorry I can't talk now cos I've booked this man for the night and I'm trying to work up the courage to perform oral sex on him".
你没必要这么说。
Well, you don't have to say that.
要我接电话吗?
Shall I answer it?
“你好,亲爱的。
"Hello, darling.
我很抱歉，但你妈妈嘴里现在有东西。”
I'm sorry but your mother has something in her mouth right now."
嘘!-“如果你愿意，我可以帮你留言。”
Shh! - "I could take your message if you would like."
听着,亲爱的,我…
Listen, darling, I...
是的。哦,是吗?哦,上帝。是的。
Yes. Oh, did he? Oh, God. Yes.
啊哈。啊哈。
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
哦，我很抱歉，是的，我明白。
Oh, I am so sorry, yes, I do understand.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
是的。
Yeah.
听着，亲爱的，我真的……帕梅拉?
Listen, darling, I really do... Pamela?
帕梅拉?
Pamela?
哦,她走了。
Oh, she's gone.
就像这样吗?没有再见?
Just like that? No goodbye?
不是电池没电了就是被绑架了。
Well, either her battery ran out or she's been abducted.
是认真的吗?她的泡菜吗?
Is it serious? Her pickle?
它是可以排序的，这是最重要的。
Well, it can be sorted, that's the main thing.
我明白了。
I see.
马修会抚养孙子孙女的，我对此毫不怀疑。
Matthew will provide the grandchildren, I've no doubt of that.
如果帕梅拉能活下来，我就很高兴了。
If Pamela can just keep herself alive, I'll be happy.
你听起来不太高兴。
You don't sound very happy.
做父母的压力很大，里奥。
Well, it's very stressful being a parent, Leo.
这种压力永远不会离开你，是…就像瘀伤上的拇指。
It's a stress that never leaves you it's... it's like a thumb on a bruise.
有时我的孩子们就像我脖子上的累赘。
Sometimes my children feel like a dead weight around my neck.
我不确定如果我知道我会不会这么做。
I'm not sure I'd have done it if I'd known.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
我是说，如果我不是一个母亲，我可以做很多其他的事情。
I mean, I could've done many other things, if I hadn't been a mother.
不然你会怎么做?——我不知道。
What else would you have done? - I dunno.
骑马穿越了沙漠……在一个炎热的小岛上建立了一个艺术家的殖民地有一个…有一个高潮……
Crossed the desert on a horse... started an artists' colony on a hot little island... had a... had an orgasm...
在这个时候，你能找到按摩服务吗?
Would you find a massage patronising at this point?
不。不,我不会。
No. No, I wouldn't.
你觉得你的孩子能感觉到吗?
Do you think your kids could feel it?
你对他们的失望?
Your disappointment in them?
我不认识里奥。我对此表示怀疑。
I don't know Leo. I doubt it.
我想他们多半没注意到我。
They mostly didn't notice me, I think.
我是说，你注意到你妈妈的失望了吗?
I mean, do you notice when your mother's disappointed?
你是担心她知道你的工作后会失望吗?
Are you worried that she'd be disappointed if she knew what you do?
我不明白你的意思。
I'm not sure what you mean.
石油钻塔没什么好失望的，女士。
There's nothing disappointing about an oil rig, ma'am.
不管怎样，你还有时间。
Anyway, there's still time for you.
哦，你真好，但是没有。
Oh, that's sweet, but there isn't.
这是它。
This is it.
我生命的最后一次尝试。
My final attempt at a life.
我是说为了高潮。
For the orgasm, I mean.
你可能不得不放弃骑马穿越沙漠。
You might have to abandon riding a horse across the desert.
我能请你帮我做件事吗?
Can I ask you to do something for me?
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
你介意把衬衫脱了吗?
Would you mind taking your shirt off?
确定。好的。
Sure. OK.
我能碰你一下吗?
Can I touch you, for a moment?
你这样…
You're just so...
我从没想过我…
I never thought I...
我能摸摸你的肩膀吗?
Can I touch your shoulders?
是的。
Yes.
和你的手臂吗?
And your arms?
是的。
Yes.
和你的胸部吗?
And your chest?
是的。
Yes.
哦。那就把它戴回去。
Oh. Put that back on then.
你想让我把它戴回去吗?
You want me to put it back on?
是的，如果你想的话。
Yes, if you want to.
我觉得事情进展得很顺利。
I thought things were progressing quite nicely.
我突然不知所措。
I was suddenly overwhelmed.
通过什么?
By what?
一些波浪，一些……欲望。
Some wave, something of... Lust.
也许吧。抱歉，我就是有点不舒服。
Maybe. Sorry, I just feel a bit sick, actually.
一点点微弱。-把头放在两腿之间。
Tiny bit faint. - Put your head between your legs.
我可以在自己的时间做。
I can do that on my own time.
我就，就…也许暂时离开一下。
I'll just, just, um... maybe step away for a moment.
喘口气。
Catch my breath.
喝一杯。
Have a drink.
只是，我，呃……我从来没感觉过你这样的人。
It's just, I, er... I've never felt anyone like you before.
喜欢我吗?-是啊，肌肉发达，身材健美。就像一个模型。
Like me? - Yeah, muscular, fit. Like a model.
我出来工作。
I work out.
我相信你会的。-我工作很努力。
I'm sure you do. - I work hard.
你不觉得有时候这有点肤浅吗?
Don't you ever feel sometimes it's a bit shallow?
是的。但我的客户很喜欢。
Yes. But my clients like it, you know.
我喜欢被他们需要。
And I like being wanted by them.
当我和你在一起，被你看着的时候，我感觉很好。
When I'm here with you, being looked at by you, I feel good.
天啊，我简直无法想象。
God, I can barely imagine that.
过来和我站在一起。
Come here and stand with me.
我一直为自己感到羞愧。我是说我的身体。
I've always been ashamed of myself. My body, I mean.
总是?
Always? - Mm.
总是意识到它的问题所在。
Always been aware of what's wrong with it.
粗短的大腿，胖胖的肚子……
You know, stubby thighs, fat tummy...
胸部下垂到我的海军，我的手臂摆动…事实上，从我20岁开始……如果我不拔这里和这里的毛，我可以在一个月后加入马戏团。
boobs come down to my naval now, my arms wobble... they have done since I was 20, actually... and if I didn't pluck here and here I could join a circus after a month.
哦，我拔了。
Oh, I've plucked it. - Mm.
别被肌肉骗了，南希。
Don't be fooled by the muscles, Nancy.
我有时也感到羞愧。
I sometimes feel ashamed too.
这很难想象。
That's hard to imagine.
如果我不是这个样子你可能就不会选择我，也不会想要我。
Well, if I didn't look like this you might not have chosen me, or wanted me.
我能解开这个吗?
Can I unbutton this?
是的。
Yes.
我能把这个拿下来吗?——嗯。
Can I take this off? - Mm-hmm.
你的身体很美。
Your body is beautiful.
我希望你能看到。
I wish you could see that.
我一直很喜欢我的小腿。
I have always quite liked my calves.
它们并不完全可怕。
They're not completely awful.
我能听到我妈妈……“虚荣是一种弱点，亲爱的。”
I can hear my mother... "Vanity is a weakness, dear."
享受你的身体不是徒劳的。
It's not vain to enjoy your body.
对它的热爱。
To love it.
但我知道你脑子里的那个声音，那个骂你的声音。
But I know that voice in your head, the one that talks shit at you.
我也有一个。
I have one too.
会累……所以无聊。
It gets tiring... so boring.
哦，我很抱歉让你厌烦了。
Oh, I'm sorry to bore you.
你不是…你没有让我厌烦，南希。
You're not... You're not boring me, Nancy.
嗯……里奥·格兰德是你的真名吗?
Hm... Is Leo Grande your real name?
不。
No.
南希·斯托克斯是你的真名吗?
Is Nancy Stokes your real name?
不。
No.
你知道吗，有时候我在想你们年轻人需要的是不是一场战争。
Do you know, sometimes I wonder whether what you young men need is a war.
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
你们都很健康而且…充满能量，在你的电脑上杀死假装的士兵，但实际上，在这一切之下，你真的很焦虑，对自己不太确定。
Well, you're all just so fit and... bursting with energy and killing pretend soldiers on your computers but actually, underneath it all, you're really quite anxious and not quite sure of yourselves.
也许这是每一代人都需要的。
Perhaps that's what every generation needs.
一场战争。这是自我校正。它让我们所有人都变得更好。
A war. It's self-correcting. It makes us all nicer.
我这一代的男人，从来没有机会证明自己。
My generation of men, they never had a chance to prove themselves.
我的意思是，我觉得她们在父亲面前觉得自己不够好。
I mean, I think they felt actually inadequate in front of their fathers.
我觉得这引起了很多麻烦我担心你的命运会更糟。
And I think it's caused a whole lot of bother and I'm worried your lot are gonna be even worse.
我哥哥在军队里。
My brother's in the army.
是吗?哦,对不起。我不是想暗示……他比你大还是比你小?
Is he? Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to imply... Is he older or younger?
他是年轻的。他是24。
He's younger. He's 24.
嗯。军队的哪一部分?
Huh. Which bit of the army?
火炮。
Artillery.
嗯，哦，大人物。
Mm, oh, the big guns.
是啊，那就全押上吧。
Yeah, well, might as well go all in.
如果我在军队，我也想要大家伙。
If I was in the army, I'd want big guns too.
你看到他了吗?——不是。
Do you see him? - Not much.
想念他吗?
Miss him?
当然可以。
Of course.
我爱他。
I love him.
和他不…他不知道这些吗?
And he doesn't... He doesn't know about all this?
不。
No.
他以为我在钻井平台工作。
He thinks I work at the oil rig.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
不确定他是否相信。
Not sure he believes it.
这么说，你们关系不近?
So, you're not close?
我能给你加满吗?
Can I top you up?
是的……请。
Yes... please.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
不是因为我。不然我就没那么开心了。
Not for me. Or I won't enjoy myself as much.
你想玩游戏吗?
You wanna play a game?
喜欢角色扮演。
Like role play.
我们可以把口交加进游戏里，可能会有帮助。
We could work the blow job into the game, it might help.
老师和学生呢?
How about teacher and student?
我们可以上一堂复习课。
We could have an RE lesson.
就像伊甸园……人类的堕落……来吧,小姐。
Like the Garden of Eden... the fall of man... Come on, Miss.
教我什么是原罪。
Teach me about original sin.
我今天表现很差，小姐。
You know, I've been very bad today, Miss.
你可能得让我下课后留下来。
You might have to keep me behind after class.
你不能再穿紧身裙了，因为我…我无法专心读圣经。
You have to stop wearing those tight skirts because I... I can't concentrate on my Bible.
你趴在我桌子上的时候我都能看到你的衬衫了。
And, er, when you lean down over my desk I can see right down your blouse.
昨晚在床上，我…好的,停止它。——但是,小姐……不，我们不应该这么做。-我知道，小姐，但是…不,不!安全词，安全词，安全词。
And last night in my bed, I... OK, stop it. - But, Miss... No, we shouldn't be doing this. - No, I know, Miss, but... No, no! Safe word, safe word, safe word.
什么?——安全的词。
What? - Safe word.
我们没有安全词。
We don't have a safe word.
我觉得我们不需要。
I didn't think we'd need one.
哦，没关系，我们可以停下来。看,我停了下来。
Oh, It's OK, we can stop. Look, I've stopped.
我只是不喜欢这些，好吗?我的上帝。
I'm just not into all that, OK? My God.
好吧,对不起。我不是故意的……我知道这看起来像什么。
OK, sorry. I didn't mean to... I-I know what this looks like.
但这不是重点。我不想支配你。
But it's just not the point. I don't want to dominate you.
我不想教你。-只是玩玩而已。
I don't want to teach you. - It's only play.
我知道，但我不想玩这个。
Yes, I know, but I don't want to play at that.
我想玩点别的。我想玩回年轻的游戏。
I want to play at something else. I want to play at feeling young again.
我想找回那种感觉。这种感觉……一切都在我面前。
I want that feeling back. That feeling of... having it all before me.
你想回到16岁吗?
You want to be 16 again?
不，我不想再回到16岁。
No, I don't want to be 16 again.
16岁真是太可怕了。
Being 16's bloody awful.
我想要回到16岁的感觉。
I want the feeling of being 16 again.
这种力量……天啊，我都不知道我有。
That power... God, I didn't know I had it.
这对我来说是浪费。
It was wasted on me.
但我教过的一些女孩…他们知道自己在做什么。
But some of the girls I taught... they knew what they were doing.
我是说男人。
With the men, I mean.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
我试着告诉她们，女孩们但是裙子一直往上，往上，往上，一直往上直到你能看到她们的后牙有多干净。
I tried to tell them, the girls but the skirts just kept on going up and up and up and up until you could practically see how clean their back teeth were.
他们根本不在乎。
They just didn't care.
为什么他们?当然，他们想穿什么就穿什么。
Why should they? They can wear what they want, surely.
男人不是总能控制自己的，里奥。他们不都像你。
Men can't always control themselves, Leo. They're not all like you.
那些男教师中有些人就像待宰的羔羊，可怜的草皮。
Some of those male teachers were like lambs to the slaughter, poor sods.
也可能是他们做错了工作。
Or maybe they were in the wrong job.
或者他们应该意识到那些女孩并没有陪伴他们。
Or maybe they should have realised those girls weren't there for them.
你有没有去过……你知道，遇到麻烦了?
Have you ever been... you know, in trouble?
在麻烦?
Been in trouble?
我是说，卖淫不是违法的吗?
Mm. I mean, isn't selling sex illegal?
不行，嫖娼是违法的。
No, soliciting money for sex is illegal.
我不是为了性而要钱，南希。
I don't solicit money for sex, Nancy.
不，我把公司卖了。
No, I sell my company.
我提供有趣的谈话。
I provide interesting conversation.
我会跳舞，我会调制20种不同的鸡尾酒。
I can dance, I can make 20 different cocktails.
我们是否做爱是我们的事。
Whether or not we have sex is our business.
这并没有什么违法的。
There's nothing illegal about that.
我的意思是，除了口交之外了解彼此也很好。
I mean, as well as the blow jobs it's also quite nice to get to know each other.
是的，我想是的。
Yes, I suppose so.
这就是为什么我倾向于推荐更多的疗程。
That's why I tend to recommend more sessions.
抱歉?
Sorry?
这让我更满足，你知道吗?
It makes it more satisfying, you know?
实际上我在寻找更多的固定客户…哦,我明白了。——什么?
I'm actually looking for more regular clients... Oh, I see. - What?
我知道这是怎么回事了。-它哪儿也不去。
I see where this is going. - It's not "going" anywhere.
它来了。强行推销。
Here it comes. The hard sell.
和驾驶课一样吗?如果我提前跟里奥·格兰德性爱学校预定的话，9块钱能买10块钱吗?
Is it like driving lessons? Do I get 10 for the price of 9 if I book in advance with the Leo Grande School of Sex?
我不知道你还有什么其他类型的客户，里奥但我不是有钱人。
I don't know what other kind of clients you have, Leo but I am not a rich woman.
不，我知道，但是…-所以，你知道，我想在我的时间、金钱和耐心耗尽之前结束销售谈话，所以……拜托，里奥·格兰德，不管你叫什么
No, I know but... - And so, you know I'd like to wind up the sales chat before my time and money and patience run out, so... please, Leo Grande, or whatever your name is
把我那该死的口活给我，我们就可以回家了。
just give me my bloody blow job and we can all go home.
为什么我不坐在边上，你可以跪在我面前的垫子上?
Why don't I sit on the edge here and you could kneel on a cushion in front of me?
你觉得怎么样?
How about that?
好的。如果这是…最优的。
OK. If that's... optimal.
我只是…把它弄出来?
Do I just... get it out?
这是正确的。
That's right.
哦,这是可悲的。我是可悲的。
Oh, it's pathetic. I'm pathetic.
那张清单真是个愚蠢的主意。
That list was such a stupid idea.
你知道，你不必做这些的。在所有。
You know, you don't have to do any of this. At all.
我很害怕。这是真相。
I'm scared. That's the truth.
的什么?
Of what?
我不会喜欢的。你不会喜欢的。
That I won't like it. That you won't like it.
也许你不会。
Maybe you won't.
但你可以试着看看。
But you can try and see.
它是无害的。
It's no harm.
除非你要咬掉它。
Unless you're gonna bite it off.
那样的话，我可能不会喜欢它。
In which case I probably won't like it.
南希，每个人都需要不同的东西。
Nancy, everyone needs something different.
也许你只是想谈谈?
Maybe you just want to talk?
我有个老客户喜欢手牵手一起看电视。
You know, I have a regular client who just likes to hold hands and watch TV together.
别误会我的意思，我还有个客户喜欢我悄无声息地走进来和她滚床单以最快的速度悄无声息地滚，然后离开。
I mean, don't get me wrong, I also have a client who likes me to walk in without a word have sex with her as quickly and silently as I can and then leave.
我其实很喜欢那部片子，因为它只需要十分钟，但她付了整整一个小时的钱。
I actually quite like that one because it only takes ten minutes but she pays for the full hour.
还有个家伙想让我打扮成一只猫然后无视他一个小时，然后回家。
And there's a guy who wants me to dress up as a cat and then ignore him for an hour and go home.
什么，不做爱吗?——没有。
What, and have no sex? - No.
不管怎样，我觉得你会成为一只很好的猫。
I think you'd make a very good cat, for what's worth.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我想说的是，我不会评判我的客户。
What I'm trying to say is, I don't judge my clients.
你知道吗?
You know?
除非他们都是混蛋。
Unless they're total arseholes.
你也不是个彻头彻尾的混蛋。
And you're definitely not a total arsehole.
很高兴听你这么说。
Well, that's nice to hear.
我有个客户不能走路了。
I have a client who can't walk.
我给她洗澡。
And I bathe her.
但她真正想要的是在我做的时候说脏话。
But what she really wants is dirty talk while I do it.
然后我和她一起下水。
And then I join her in the water.
这是她想要的。
It's what she wants.
嗯。-每个人都想要不同的东西。
Hmm. - Everyone wants something different.
你听起来像个性爱圣人。
You sound like some sort of sex saint.
你是真实的吗?
Are you real?
哦，不，我真的很喜欢她。
Oh no, I really fancy her.
很热。
It's quite hot.
我很期待。
And I look forward to it.
这是她需要的。
It's what she needs.
你说得好像它应该从地方议会那里得到。
You make it sound like it should be available from the local council.
就像公共服务。
Like a public service.
你能想象这样会少多少废话吗?
Mm. Can you imagine how much less bullshit there would be?
只要他们不提高利率因为人们对此已经足够愤怒了。
As long as they don't put the rates up cos people are furious enough about that.
他们还是会捡垃圾桶。
They'll still collect the bins.
但在你这行，女人就不一样了，不是吗?
It's different for women, though, in your line of work, isn't it?
更加危险。-可以。
More dangerous. - It can be.
好吧，我也被人骂过几次还被人扇过耳光。
Well, I've been called some choice names and been slapped about a bit.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
哦,来吧。你知道的。你做的事情。
Oh, come on. You know that. You do.
是啊，你知道我以前在道德课上就布置过这样的论文题目。
Yeah, you know I used to set this exact essay question in my ethics lessons.
“性工作应该合法化吗?”
"Should sex work be made legal?"
每年都有30篇文章寄回来，都一模一样。
And every year, 30 essays came back, all exactly the same.
他们说了什么?
What did they say?
虽然道德问题仍有待讨论，但性工作合法化最终会为性工作者提供保护，并有助于根除贩运和虐待。
Uh, that although the moral issues remain up for debate the legalisation of sex work would ultimately provide protection for sex workers and help eradicate trafficking and abuse.
听起来像维基百科。
Sounds like Wikipedia.
这是维基百科。他们都一字不差地抄下来了。
It is Wikipedia. They all copied it out, word for word.
每年。除了一个叫卢卡斯·怀特的男孩，他写了…“性工作应该合法化，这样你妈妈才能为她的收入纳税。”
Every year. Except this one boy Lucas White who wrote, um... "Sex work should be made legal so your mum pays tax on her earnings."
说实话，这倒是让我松了一口气。
Which did provide a bit of light relief if I'm honest.
哦……
Oh...
我认为这是…比这大得多，整个想法。
I think it's... much bigger than that, the whole idea.
试想一下，如果所有人都能享受到，那该有多文明啊没有羞耻感，没有评判。
Just think how civilised it could be if it was just available to all there's no shame attached, there's no judgement.
你想要性，但你因为某种原因无法得到而感到沮丧。
You want sex, and you're frustrated you can't get it for whatever reason.
你害羞，你不舒服，你悲伤，你身体挣扎……所以你就雇我这样的人。
You're shy, you're unwell, you're grieving you're physically struggling... so you just hire someone like me.
这些都是规范的，安全的。
It's all regulated and safe.
对你，对我，对大家都好。
For you, for me, better for everyone.
我帮你…或者我让你高兴。
And I help you... Or I pleasure you.
那就更好了。
Even better.
…问题是，很多人喜欢保密。
The... thing is, lots of people like the secrecy.
他们很享受，或者他们只是想要幻想。
They get off on it, or they just want the fantasy.
这完全没问题，但是…我很喜欢现实，这是我真正的工作，所以……
And that's totally fine but... I quite like the reality and it's my actual job, so...
南希，你知道吗，我喜欢的一件事，就是当一个人感到高兴时，观察他的表情。
You know, one thing I love, Nancy, is just to watch someone's face when they feel pleasure.
当他们放手的时候，当他们屈服的时候，当身体随之而去的时候，那种热度，那种感觉……
When they let go, when they succumb when the body goes with it and that heat, and that feeling...
一切都只是放松。
Everything just loosens.
这是……
It's...
真是太棒了。
It's just so, so great.
哦!
Oh!
你确实喜欢。
You do like it.
谢谢你告诉我这些，里奥。
Thank you for telling me that, Leo.
我的意思是，不仅因为它非常有趣和有启发性……
I mean, not only because it was very interesting and enlightening...
但也…你介意……吗?就去做吧。
But also... do you mind if... Go for it.
这是一个惊喜。
That was a surprise.
一个好的惊喜?
A good surprise?
是的,非常好。我不确定。
Yes, very good. I wasn't sure about it.
你知道的，不管我是否喜欢，但是…就像在温暖的大海里沐浴。
You know, whether I'd like it, but it's... like bathing in a warm sea.
实际上，我可能是睡着了一会儿。对不起。
I may have dropped off for a moment, actually. Sorry.
这是没有问题。
It's no problem.
但也没有…-没有高潮，没有。
But also no... - No, no orgasm, no.
我想知道我会发出什么样的声音。
I wonder what noise I'd make.
显然打喷嚏是一个人高潮时声音有多大的一个很好的信号。
Apparently sneezing's a very good sign of how loud a person is when they orgasm.
真的吗?-是的。
Really? - Yeah.
我妈妈打喷嚏的声音很大。
My mother sneezes very loudly.
但是有些人会像猫一样打喷嚏。
But some people sneeze like cats.
你知道的…我…我永远无法摆脱这样的想法:它们也必须像猫一样高潮。
You know... I... I can never rid myself of the notion that they must orgasm like cats too.
如果猫高潮。我不知道，他们呢?
If cats orgasm. I don't know, do they?
没有人知道。
Nobody knows.
你是怎么假装的，和你丈夫?你发出了什么声音?
How did you fake it, with your husband? What noise did you make?
嗯,哦,上帝…等待。我得想想……想清楚，嗯……
Um, oh, God... Wait. I've got to think... think it through, um...
Hm-hm-hm-hm。
Hm-hm-hm-hm.
这很有说服力。
That was very convincing.
无论如何……这是遗愿清单上的第二项。
Anyway... that's number two ticked off the bucket list.
或者“从操你妈的名单上舔下来”。
Or "licked off the fuck-it list".
相当。我对此非常高兴。
Quite. And I'm very happy about that.
你在这方面做得很好。
You are very good at this whole business, you know.
我希望你知道。人们应该告诉你。
I hope you know. People should tell you.
谢谢你！很高兴听你这么说。
Thank you. That's nice to hear.
这是一种神秘的天赋。
It's a sort of mysterious gift you have.
这并不是那么神秘。我只是努力而已。
It's not so mysterious. I just make the effort.
我喜欢你，所以很简单。
And I like you, so it's easy.
看,看到了什么?你总是知道什么时候该采取行动，什么时候该说什么。
See, see? You always know the right thing to say when to make the move and all that.
你要学会读懂别人。
You learn to read people.
我不确定我是否有过。
I'm not sure I ever have.
首先你得想这么做。
You have to want to first.
是的，我可能不想足够投入工作。
Yeah, I probably don't want to enough to put in the work.
我只是注意。
I just pay attention.
你呢?有人在关注你吗?
And what about you? Is there someone who pays attention to you?
你知道，有人吗?——有人吗?
You know, is there someone? - Someone?
是的，你知道，一个特别的人，一个特别的人。
Yes, you know, a special person, a particular person.
什么，除了你?
What, other than you?
哦,阻止它。我是说女朋友，男朋友或者，你懂的，就是你现在那种不固定的安排。
Oh, stop it. I mean a girlfriend, or boyfriend or, you know, one of those fluid arrangements you have these days.
南希。——狮子座。
Nancy. - Leo.
一切都是为了此刻，在这个房间里，此刻。
It's all about this moment, in this room, right now.
一切都围绕着你。
It's all about you.
忘记一切。这就是重点。
Forget everything else. That's the whole point.
没错，但你在里面是谁?
Yes, but who are you in there?
你是谁?这就是我想知道的。
Who are you out there? That's what I want to know.
现在我已经为你重新预订了。-我很高兴你这么做了。
Now I've rebooked you. - And I'm very glad you did.
我也是，但我想也许我们可以把它个性化一点。
And I am too, but I just thought maybe we could personalise it a bit.
如果这是常事的话。
If it's gonna be a regular thing.
我以为你对我的工作很满意。
I thought you were happy with what I'm doing.
我的天啊，相信我。
Oh my goodness, believe me, I am.
我的身体不再是我拖了三十年的尸体了。
My body is no longer the carcass I've been heaving around for thirty years.
不，它现在是一个奇迹。
No, it's now a thing of wonder.
就像你说的"欢乐的游乐场"
"A playground of delight", as you say.
我说过吗?
Did I say that?
嗯,也许不是。但是你呢?
Mm, perhaps not. But what about you?
真实的你?
The real you?
我就是你想要的样子…就在这里，就在此刻。
I'm whatever you want me to be... here, in this moment.
但如果我想知道没有我的你是谁呢?
Hmm, but what if I want to know who you are without me?
当我不在的时候。
When I'm not there.
那不是也可以吗?
Wouldn't that be OK too?
南希，我希望我给了你我说给你的。
Nancy, I hope I've given you what I said I would give you.
你说过我们应该互相了解。
You said we should get to know each other.
南希。
Nancy.
所以你不打算告诉我。
So you're not going to tell me.
嘿，你考虑过用性玩具吗?
Hey, have you ever considered using sex toys?
其实我带了一些，因为有些人觉得这样更容易……-如果是这样的话，我有话要对你说。
You know, I actually brought some with me because some people find it much easier... - Actually, in that case I've got something to tell you.
噢,是吗?——是的。
Oh, yeah? - Yes.
好吧，接着说。
Well, go on then.
你知道的，如果你什么都不告诉我独自度过漫漫长夜…好奇心占了上风……现在吗?——是的。它的功能。
Well, you know, if you're not gonna tell me anything yourself long nights alone... one's curiosity gets the better of one... Does it now? - Yes. It does.
我知道你是谁。
I know who you are.
抱歉?
Sorry?
我知道你是谁。我发现了你在现实生活中的身份。
I know who you are. I found out who you are in real life.
不知道你在说什么。这就是我。
Don't know what you mean. This is who I am.
不，我是说你的真名。我知道你的真名了。
No, I mean your real name. I found out your real name.
我本来想早点告诉你的，但是…但是……?
I was gonna tell you earlier, but... But...?
但我觉得最好…………他妈的第一?
But I thought it was best to... To... fuck first?
我只是做了一点小小的侦查。
Well, it was just a minor bit of sleuthing on my part.
你知道，在我的信用卡对账单上，你的网站上有一个公司，你只要去该公司的网站，你就可以找到该公司董事的名字
You know, on my credit card statement there's a company listed to your website and you just go to the company's house website and you can find the name of the director of the company
所以我才知道了你的名字，你的真名
and that's how I found out your name, you real name.
坚持下去。
Hang on.
等等，怎么了?
Hold on, what's going on?
不,我……如果你愿意，我可以告诉你我的真名?
No, I'll... I'll tell you my real name, if you like?
我不介意。-不，谢谢，我没兴趣。
I don't mind. - No, thank you, I'm not interested.
也没那么糟，不是吗?
Well, it's not so bad, is it?
让我知道，我是说，它…我们又不是陌生人。
For me to know, I mean, it... It's not as if we're strangers.
我有边界。
I have boundaries.
我要求你尊重他们。你没有，所以我现在要走了。请不要再试图预定我了。
I've asked you to respect them. You haven't so I'll be going now. Please don't attempt to book me again.
哦，得了吧。
Oh, come on now.
来吧。没那么糟。我将……我会忘记我说过的。
Come on. It's not so bad. I'll... I'll forget I mentioned it.
不。
No.
我还是会叫你“里奥”。
I'll still call you "Leo".
你不会给我打电话，因为我不在这里。
You won't calling me anything because I won't be here.
好的,康纳。
OK, Connor.
别这么叫我。
Don't you call me that.
我叫里奥·格兰德。
My name is Leo Grande.
你预定了里奥·格兰德，你就得到了里奥·格兰德。
You booked Leo Grande, and you got Leo Grande.
从这些呻吟和叹息中我能看出你对里奥·格兰德并无怨言，对吗?
And from what I could tell by the moans and the sighs you have no complaints with Leo Grande, am I right?
是的。——好。
Yes. - Good.
所以我们很清楚。
So we're clear on that.
这是里奥·格兰德。我创造了他，我为他感到骄傲。
This is Leo Grande. I made him, and I'm proud of him.
顺便说一句，南希·斯托克斯
And by the way, "Nancy Stokes"
我自己就能知道你是谁。
I could find out who you are myself, you know.
你认为如果人们知道他们的前re老师在酒店房间里雇佣年轻人舔他们的阴部，他们会作何反应?
How do you think people would react if they knew their ex-RE teacher was hiring young men to lick their pussy in a hotel room?
什么?这对你来说太真实了吗?
What? Is that a little too real for you?
因为我们一直都是这么做的，所以现在别太紧张了。
Cos that's just what we've just been doing, so don't get squeamish now.
我真的没想到你会有这样的反应。
I honestly didn't think you'd react like this.
什么?-我还以为你会高兴呢
What? - Well, I thought you'd be pleased.
高兴吗?
Pleased?
我以为我们建立起了信任，真正的信任。
Well, I thought we'd built up a trust, a real trust.
我已经准备好告诉你我是谁了。
I mean, I was ready to tell you who I am.
我想我们可以在外面继续，喝杯咖啡什么的。
I thought we could maybe continue outside of here, have a coffee or a drink or something.
为什么我们不能呢?
Why can't we?
为什么我们不能做朋友?
Why can't we be friends?
我是说，是因为我老了吗?
I mean, is it cos I'm old?
因为老太太不允许参与任何需要保持安静和被宠爱的活动，直到…直到你需要我们的钱然后你就会出现，做任何事。
Cos old ladies aren't allowed to participate in anything where have to be kept quiet and cosseted until... oh, until you need our money and then you'll turn up and do anything.
听着，我知道和你的孩子在一起是什么感觉，但我从来没有把你当作一个老……我以为你对你的工作很自豪。
Look, I know that's how it feels with your kids but I have never treated you or thought of you like an old... I thought you were proud of your work.
你为什么感到羞愧?
Why are you ashamed?
我不羞愧。
I'm not ashamed.
但你在撒谎，你隐藏了自己，还有你的工作。
But you're lying about it, you're hiding yourself, and your work.
即使是你最亲近的人。
Even from those closest to you.
你欺骗。你疯了，被蒙蔽了。
You're deluded. You're crazy and deluded.
如果你这么骄傲，为什么你妈妈不知道真相?
Why can't your mother know the truth if you're so proud?
如果你不觉得羞愧的话。-你知道有个词可以形容这个。
If you're not ashamed. - You know there's a word for this.
它叫做网络狩猎。疯子会这么做。
It's called cyber-stalking. And nutters do it.
像你这样疯狂，悲伤，绝望的疯子。
Crazy, sad, desperate nutters like you.
好吧，我很抱歉我竟然厚颜无耻地查出了过去一个月和我发生关系的男人的真实身份。
Oh, well, I am so sorry that I had the audacity to find out the true identity of the man I've been having sex with for the past month.
跟我说说你在石油钻井上的生活吧?
Why don't you tell me more about your life on the oil rig?
你为什么要对我隐瞒你的身份?
Why do you have to lie to me about who you are?
我没骗你，南希!
I am not lying to you, Nancy!
这是我的专业名字。
This is my professional name.
我提供一种服务，一种幻想，我跟你说得很清楚了。
I provide a service, a fantasy, and I told you that very clearly.
你说那是一种职业。
Well, all that stuff you said about it being a vocation.
这是谎言吗?——没有。
Is that lies? - No.
她一定会为你感到骄傲的。她会。
She would be proud of you, surely. She would.
我们为什么要谈论我母亲?
Why are we talking about my mother?
我可以和她谈谈。我一直和父母相处得很好。
I could talk to her. I was always very good with the parents.
我可以向她解释，我可以让她明白。
I could explain it to her, I could make her understand.
不了,谢谢。
No, thank you.
我认为这很重要。让我来做。-我不需要你这么做。
I think it's important. Let me do it. - I don't need you to do that.
好吧，让我试试。我觉得这对你的生活有好处。
Well, let me try. I think it would be good for you for your life.
没人跟我妈解释因为在她看来，我已经死了。
Nobody is explaining anything to my mother because far as she's concerned, I'm dead.
对不起,什么?什么?什么?-是的。
Sorry, what? What? What? - Yeah.
她对每个人都这么说。
That's what she tells everyone.
在那里。
There.
你现在觉得性感吗?
Do you feel sexy now?
感觉这就是你花钱买的东西吗?
Feel like that's what you're paying for?
不，我不这么认为。
No, I didn't think so.
听着，南希，我很遗憾你的儿子如此无趣而你女儿的生活却比你精彩。
Look, Nancy, I'm sorry that your son is so immensely boring and that your daughter has a more exciting life than you.
你说你的孩子就像你脖子上的累赘所以我们不要假装你自己就是"年度最佳母亲"对吧?
You said your kids are like a dead weight around your neck so let's not pretend you're exactly "Mother of the Year" yourself, right?
但她为什么要你死?为什么?你对她做了什么?
But why would she want you dead? Why? What did you do to her?
滚蛋,南希。
Fuck off, Nancy.
好吧。
Alright.
别跟我说话，我只是忘带手机了。
Don't talk to me, I just forgot my phone.
他妈的。
Fuck.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
他妈的。
Fuck.
请利奥。请。——操!
Leo, please. Please. - Fuck!
你想知道我妈妈会不会为我感到骄傲?
You wanna know if my mother would be proud of me?
是的，她和我断绝关系了。
Yeah, she disowned me.
她让我一个人自谋生路。
She left me to fend for myself.
你当时多大?
How old were you?
我15岁。
I was 15.
为什么?她为什么和你断绝关系?你做了什么?
Why? Why did she disown you? What did you do?
我做了什么?
What did I do?
我只是让她失望了。
I just disappointed the fuck out of her.
喂?
Hello?
不，是的，不，不，不。它很好。
No, yes, no, no, no. It's fine.
是我的朋友，他，嗯…他摔倒了，伤到了膝盖。是的。
It's my friend, he, um... he fell, actually, hurt his knee. Yes.
当然不是。我们会小声点的。
Absolutely, no, of course. We'll keep it down.
是的,是的,抱歉。谢谢。
Yes, yes, sorry. Thanks.
再见。
Bye.
我妈妈和你一样。
You know, my mother was like you.
她每件事都做对了。
She did everything right.
桌上的食物，抽屉里的干净衣服，所有这些，但是嗯…我觉得她从来没有…从没见过我。
Food on the table, clean clothes in the drawers, all that, but um... I don't think she ever... ever actually saw me.
就算她知道，她也不喜欢。
Or if she did, she didn't like it.
你知道，她试图隐藏她的厌恶，但我能感觉到…隔着墙振动，然后…我只是…我不是她想要的。她对自己的想象。
You know, she tried to hide her repulsion but I could just feel it... vibrating through the walls, and... I just... I wasn't what she wanted. What she imagined for herself.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
好吧，你可以不要对我指指点点我的生活，我的工作。
Yeah, well, you can quit judging me you know, my life, my work.
你根本不关心我生活的真相。
You don't actually care about the truth of my life.
你只是想要一些东西…异国情调。
You just wanted something... exotic.
一个破破烂烂的小婊子。
A broken little whore.
我猜你找到他了。
And I guess you found him.
你做得好。
Well done you.
我要走了，南希。
I'm gonna leave now, Nancy.
到时你可以退款。
You can have a refund on the time.
你需要什么吗?
Can I get you anything?
不，谢谢，我在等人。
No, thanks, I'm waiting for someone.
好的。
OK.
你需要什么吗?-我说了不……哦，对不起，你是另一个人。
Can I get you anything? - I said no tha... Oh, sorry, you're a different one.
非常感谢，我在等人。
Thanks a lot, I'm waiting for someone.
你等的时候需要点什么吗?-没什么，谢谢。
Can I get you anything while you wait? - Nothing, thank you.
我能帮你…-不用了，谢谢。对不起。
Can I get you... - No, thank you. Sorry.
谢谢，不，我在等，我会等，我会等我的朋友。
Thank you, no, I'm waiting, I will wait, I will wait for my friend.
你以前教过我。
Oh, you used to teach me.
抱歉?-是的。
Sorry? - Yeah.
罗宾逊夫人。再保险。
Mrs Robinson. RE.
小点声，好吗?
Oh, keep your voice down a little, would you?
那你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here then?
我要去见一个朋友。是的。
Um, ah, well, I'm meeting a friend. Yeah.
因为这里的停车很好。
Cos the parking here's so good.
这肯定比咖啡好。
Well, it's certainly better than the coffee.
我是贝基·福斯特，你还记得我吗?
I'm Becky Foster, do you remember me?
嗯,不,实际上。我…有趣的是，我不知道。
Um, no, actually. I... funnily enough, I don't.
对不起。-是的，你在我八年级的时候教过我。
Sorry. - Yeah, you used to teach me in Year 8.
我了吗?我不可能把你教得很好，对吧?
Did I? I can't have taught you very well, could I?
为什么?-因为你在这里工作。
Why's that? - Cos you're working here.
你好。
Hello.
哦!
Oh!
你从哪里来?
Where did you come from?
嗯…-这是你的朋友?
Um... - This your friend, then?
是的,他是……嗯…-我想卖掉我的车。
Yeah, well, he's... Well... - Uh, I'm trying to sell my car.
这位好心的女士很感兴趣所以我们觉得这是个见面看看它的好地方。
Um, this good lady is interested so we thought this was a great place to meet to have a look at it.
嗯。因为停车场很好。
Mm. Mm-hmm. Cos the parking's so good.
这肯定比咖啡好。
Well, it's certainly better than the coffee.
不管怎样，我们要两杯咖啡。
We'll take two of those coffees, anyway.
我们愿意冒这个险。谢谢你！
We'll take the risk. Thank you.
我们坐吗?
Shall we sit?
是的。
Yeah.
你来了。
You came.
你订了。
You booked.
我没想到你会。
I didn't think you would.
我也不确定自己会不会。
I wasn't sure I would either.
但我们都知道今天的交易。
But we both know the deal today.
不过，我还是很高兴你决定来，只是谈谈。
Still, I'm very glad that you decided to come, just to talk.
可爱。
Lovely.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这是一件很强大的事情。
It's a powerful thing.
性满足。
Sexual fulfilment.
它让你觉得……这让我觉得自己是无敌的。
It makes you feel... Well, it made me feel invincible.
我没有意识到。
I hadn't realised.
我希望我年轻的时候早点知道。
I wish I'd known sooner, when I was younger.
我会做出必要的改变。
I'd have made the necessary changes.
至少你现在已经做到了。
At least you've done that now.
是的。是的。
Yes. Yes.
你知道，在过去的一个月里，我觉得自己比以往任何时候都更有活力，更有力量。
And you know, I have felt more alive and more powerful in this last month than I can ever remember.
我的意思是，我看到我的朋友…在边缘逐渐消失。
I mean, I see my friends... fading away at the edges.
只是干瘪了这么多年，我想…事实上，你是对的，里奥，这应该是一项公共服务。
Just shrivelling up over the years and I think... actually, you're right, Leo, this should be a public service.
你跟几个人提过我。你的朋友。
You told a couple of them about me. Your friends.
是的，我给伟大的里奥·格兰德提过建议。
Yes, I have made recommendations for the great Leo Grande.
我告诉他们你是更年期的专家。
I told them you're the master of the menopause.
我会写在我的名片上。
I'll put it on my business card.
当然，我一直很谨慎。
I've been very discreet of course.
我只告诉了我认为真正需要的人…需要它…你……需要你。
I've only told the ones I thought could really use... Need it... You... Need you.
我很感激。
Well, I appreciate that.
嗯…里奥，我的真名是苏珊·罗宾逊。
Uh... Leo, my name, my real name is Susan Robinson.
好无聊的名字，不是吗?
Such a boring name, isn't it?
罗宾逊夫人。嗯。这是可爱的。
Mrs Robinson. Hmm. That's cute.
我这辈子从来没做过什么有趣或了不起的事。
I've never done anything interesting or remarkable in my life.
嗯，就是这个。
Um, this is it.
我总是遵守所有的规则。
I always obeyed all the rules fell in line.
我从不酗酒，从不在派对上盖过我丈夫。
I never drank too much, never overshadowed my husband at parties.
我总是被指定为司机。
I was always the designated driver.
我一天吃五块。
Ate my five a day.
甚至在它们被称为“一天五个”之前。
Even before they were called "five a day."
电话一响，我就接。
And I always, always answer my phone when it rings.
你是我唯一的冒险。
You're the only adventure I've ever had.
唯一的自由，还有……我希望它是真实的。
The only freedom, and... I wanted it to be real.
我没有好好考虑这件事。
I wasn't thinking about it properly.
我发烧发疯了……欲望等等。
I was mad with some fever... lust or whatever.
这让我很生气。
It made me mad.
我从来没有……我从来没有……
I never... I've never...
对不起,狮子座。
I'm sorry, Leo.
我很……
I'm so...
就是这样。-就是这样。
That's it. - Mm. That's it.
我只是想看看你，看看你一切都好。
I just wanted to see you, see you were alright.
告诉你你为我做了什么。
Tell you what you've done for me.
向你表示感谢和告别。
To thank you and to say goodbye.
一切都好吗，罗宾逊太太?
Everything OK here, Mrs Robinson?
是的，谢谢。我们刚刚结束。
Yes, um, thank you. We're just wrapping up here now.
罗宾逊太太以前在学校教我如何使用英语。
Mrs Robinson used to teach me RE at school.
噢,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
谢谢你,贝基。
Thank you, Becky.
——是的。她是个好老师吗?
- Yes. - Was she a good teacher?
她是好的。有些紧张。
She was alright. Bit uptight.
不像其他人那么糟糕。——嗯。
Not as bad as some of the others. - Uh-huh.
是的。除了这一次…谢谢你，贝琪，谢谢你的报告。
Yeah. Except for this one time... Thank you, Becky, for that glowing report.
她把我们所有女孩都召集在一起举行了一个特别集会。
She got all us girls together for a special assembly.
贝基……-不，不，继续。
Becky... - No, no, go on.
她说我们都是荡妇。
And she told us we were all sluts.
我觉得事情不是这样的，贝琪。
I don't think that's quite what happened, Becky.
是的，她说女孩应该看起来体面，否则我们就会到处引诱男人，让自己陷入麻烦。
Yeah, she said girls should look respectable or we would go around tempting the men and get ourselves into trouble.
她说如果我们看起来像荡妇，就会被当作荡妇对待。
She said if we looked like sluts, we'd be treated like sluts.
嗯，这主要和裙子的长度有关，那时候裙子的长度已经失控了。
Well, it was to do with the length of the skirts mostly which had just got out of control by then.
他说如果我们花在学习上的时间和花在头发上的时间一样多，我们都会过得更好。
Said if we spent as much time on our studies as we did on our hair, we'd all be a lot better off.
嗯，事实上，我想……我支持这一点。我支持这一点。
Well, actually, I do... I stand by that. I stand by that.
“贪心”。
"Concupiscence".
也要永远记住这一点。
Always remember that, too.
她常常让我们说……她说她喜欢这个名字。
She used to make us say... Said she liked the sound of it.
我也做。
I did too.
听你这么说我很高兴。这是个好词。
Well, I'm glad to hear it. It's a good word.
-什么意思?——“欲望”。
- What does it mean? - "Lustful desire".
哦。嗯,很好。现在你说话。
Oh. Well, well. Now you're talking.
是的，希波的圣奥古斯丁在他的原罪学说中创造了这个词。
Mm. Yes, St Augustine of Hippo coined the term in his doctrine of original sin.
他相信它支撑着世界上所有的苦难和罪恶。
He believed that it underpins all the suffering and sins in the world.
贝琪，能把账单给我们吗?
So Becky, could we please have that bill?
我觉得我不能同意因为我一点都不懂"概念"
Well, I don't think I can go along with that cos it doesn't make any "Concupi-sense" to me at all.
我知道的最长的单词。
Longest word I know.
请结账，贝基!
The bill, please, Becky!
我的遗产。作为一个教育家。
My legacy. As an educator.
“贪心”。这是一个好词。
"Concupiscence". It is a good word.
这对我来说是一个新的问题。
It's a new one on me.
我很高兴找到了一个你不知道的。
Oh, well, I'm glad to have found one you didn't know.
我希望我能。
I was hoping I would.
我…我告诉了我哥哥。
I... I told my brother.
关于我的工作。
About what I do.
他说了什么?
What did he say?
他听到我大声说出来很惊讶。
Well, he was surprised to hear me say it, out loud.
但他猜我是用这种东西赚钱的。
But he guessed I made money with something like this.
他说他好像已经知道了。
He, um, he said he kind of already knew.
他从来不相信钻井平台的故事。
And he never believed the oil rig stories.
他说妈妈永远不会提起我。
He said Mum would never talk about me.
关于她所看到的。发生了什么。
About what she saw. About what happened.
我想我对我妈来说有点太疯狂了。
Guess I was a bit wild for my mum.
她有很多事情要处理。
A lot for her to handle.
有一天晚上，那时我想…她周末出去了。
There was this one night, back then when I thought... uh, she was gone out for the weekend.
但我错了，嗯…考试后我叫了一些朋友过来玩，我们放了些音乐，喝了些酒……然后我就知道，她和邻居撞见我和我的朋友们
But I was wrong, um... I had some friends over to hang out after exams we put on some music, drank some wine... Next thing I know, she and a neighbour are walking in on me and my friends
和我们都是……尸体裹在一起，一切都在发生。
and we're all... bodies wrapped up together, bit of everything going on.
嗯…互相探索。
Um... exploring each other.
我永远不会忘记她的脸。
And I'll never forget her face.
只是羞辱。因此蒙羞。
Just humiliated. So ashamed.
之后的几周我们都想和好，但是…她浑身上下都是厌恶。
We tried for weeks after to patch things up, but, um... her disgust was just all over her.
我…不得不离开。
I... had to leave.
她说她很高兴我要去而且她再也不会提我的名字了。
She, um, said she was glad I was going and that she would never speak my name again.
从那时起，她告诉所有人她儿子就是在那天去世的。
And from that point on she told everyone that that was the day her son had died.
当然，当然，时间是一个伟大的……治疗者?是的。-…医治者。
Surely, surely, time's a great... Healer? Yeah. - ...healer.
不,南希,她……她的意思。
No, Nancy, she... she meant it.
几年前我还在街上见过她。
I even saw her a couple of years ago in the street.
她只是……她径直从我身边走过。
She just... she walked straight past me.
是的,只是冷。
Yeah, just cold.
你会这样对自己的儿子吗?
Would you do that to your own son?
只是因为他太平凡了，我可能没注意到他。
Well, only because he's so unremarkable I might not notice him.
我不应该再那样说他了。
I should probably stop saying things like that about him.
是啊，也许你应该这么做。
Yeah, you probably should.
不，他是个好孩子，有他在我很幸运。
No, he's a good boy and I'm very lucky to have him.
她错了，你母亲。
She was wrong, your mother.
你没有什么让人恶心或失望的。
There is nothing disgusting or disappointing about you.
谢谢你,贝基。
Thank you, Becky.
贝琪，你能等一下吗?
Becky, could you wait a moment?
贝琪，我想向你道歉。
Becky, I would like to apologise to you.
什么?——是的。
What? - Yes.
我欠你一个道歉。
I owe you an apology.
叫你荡妇。这是错误的。
For calling you a slut. That was wrong.
我不应该对一群易受影响的少女使用这个词或想法。
That was not a word or idea I should have used with a group of impressionable teenage girls.
我当时以为我做的是对的……我想保护你，但现在…
I thought I was doing the right thing at the time... trying to protect you, but now...
但是现在,我…
But now, I...
贝基……我不是来买这个人的车的。
Becky... I am not here to buy this man's car.
好的。
OK.
这是里奥·格兰德，他是一个…
This is Leo Grande and he is a...
我是性工作者。
I'm a sex worker.
是的。是的。
Yes. Yes.
过去几周我们经常见面做爱。
And we have been meeting for sex regularly for the past few weeks.
——这是正确的。-没错，没错
- That's right. - That's right, that's right.
我非常推荐他因为他的舌头绝对是一个奇迹。
And, um, I recommend him highly cos from anything else he's an absolute marvel with his tongue.
贝琪，你可能已经知道了我希望你知道，但快乐是件很棒的事。
And, um, Becky, you may already know this I hope you do, but pleasure is a wonderful thing.
这是我们每个人都应该拥有的。
It's something we should all have.
嗯…如果你不介意的话，我在楼上订了个房间，里奥和我要走了，如果我们想在剩下的时间里安排一个疗程的话，因为，嗯……
Um... If you'll excuse us uh, I have a room booked upstairs and um, Leo and I need to get going if we want to fit a session in in the remaining time cos, um...
.．.有几件事我想试试。
...there's a couple of things I'd like to try.
很高兴认识你，贝琪。
It was great to meet you, Becky.
我希望我们有机会再见面。
I hope maybe we'll run into each other again sometime.
不用找了。
Keep the change.
脱了吧，南希·斯托克斯。
Take those off, Nancy Stokes.
我不能落下帷幕……我不能这样平衡。我不能平衡。
I can't bal... I can't balance like this. I can't balance.
好的。
OK.
哦,哦……
Oh-oh...
是吗?
Did you?
停止问。
Stop asking.
好的。——你念念不忘的。
OK. - You're fixated.
我觉得你应该放弃。
I think you should drop it.
我知道我知道我只是…没有压力，当然，我只是希望。
I know, I know, I just... There's no pressure, of course, I was just hoping.
也许其他人都是装的。
Maybe all the others are faking.
你想过吗?
Have you ever thought of that?
不。——我在开玩笑。
No. - I'm joking.
我们再试一次。只是为了好玩。
We'll try one more time. Just for fun.
哦,好吧。如果你一定要……
Oh, OK. If you must...
闭上你的眼睛。
Close your eyes.
等等，我带了些东西，你可能想尝尝。
Hang on, I brought something with me that you might like to try.
哦，你知道吗?
Oh, you know what?
里奥，我想我做不到。
Leo, I don't think I can.
…我想我讲完了。
I... I think I'm done.
我还以为我带了那个小家伙。
I thought I brought the little bugger.
它通常的作品。
It usually works.
在这儿。
Here it is.
那是……
Was that...
里奥，我想这是我们最后一次见面了。
Leo, I think this should be the last time we meet.
很高兴您为我预约了。
I'm glad you booked me.
我很高兴你来了。-我很高兴你来了。
I'm glad you came. - I'm glad you came.
对吧?
Right?
可以这样说，我是非常满意的顾客。
I'm very satisfied customer, put it like that.
我将在反馈表上的绿色笑脸上打勾。
I shall be ticking the big green smiley face on the feedback form.
好的。
OK.
嗯…嗯…那么再见了，里奥·格兰德。
Well... Well... Good bye, then, Leo Grande.
祝你好运。
And good luck to you.
Good luck to you.
照顾,南希。
Take care, Nancy.
♪我，我想我很沮丧♪想到所有的地方♪
♪ I, I guess I'm frustrated ♪ Thinking about all the places ♪
♬我现在应该在♬我在无尽的等待♪感觉就像一桶炸药等待火焰的到来♪
♪ I should've been by now ♪ And I'm endlessly waiting ♪ Feel like a barrel of dynamite waiting for a flame to come 'round ♪
♪我需要一点火花♪黑暗里的一盏灯我想我准备好了我想我准备好了
♪ I need a little spark ♪ A light in bitter dark ♪ I think I'm ready to go I think I'm ready ♪
我想我准备好了我想我准备好了
♪ I think I'm ready to go I think I'm ready ♪
♬而我在悬崖边上
♪ And I'm at the edge of the cliff ♪
我们开始吧我想我准备好了，我想我准备好了
♪ So let's begin ♪ I think I'm ready to go, I think I'm ready ♪